我的意识要我说不
My mind is tellin me no
但是我的身体  我的身体却在叫我说好
but my body, my body's tellin me yes
宝贝  我不想伤害任何人
Baby, I don't want to hurt nobody
但是有些事情我必须坦白
But there is something that I must confess
有点小小的磕磕碰碰
I don't see nothing wrong
我觉得没什么不好
with a little bump and grind
有点小小的磕磕碰碰
I don't see nothing wrong
他睡着了没
Is he asleep yet?
睡着了  我去把他放床上
Yeah, I'll go put him to bed.
罗伯特?凯利真是屡试不爽
R. Kelly always does the trick.
我觉得伊凡可能在发疹
I think Evan may be developing a rash.
你给他的屁股涂婴儿润肤膏时
You know, when you rub the Aquaphor on his tush,
不能只涂在臀瓣上
you can't just put it on his cheeks,
肛门上也得整个涂满
you have to rub it all over the anus, too.
整个肛门  明白了
All over the anus, got it.
我先去洗个澡吧
I think I'm going to take a bath, okay?
去洗吧  宝贝
Okay, babe. Go for it.
这次可不能被逮到了
Not this time.
好  来吧  来吧  来吧
Okay, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on. Okay.
好
Yep.
劲爆大学骚货
你喜欢淫荡点的  是吗
Oh, yeah, you like it nasty, don't you?
那是  那是  我忏悔我有罪
Oh, I do. I do, I'm sorry. Guilty as charged.
你真大  撑的我痛了
God, you're so big, it hurts.
我知道  没办法啊
I know, I can't help it.
亲爹地 快射吧
Give it to me, daddy. Oh, yeah.
快射吧  爹地  快射吧
Give it to me, daddy. Give it to me... Oh, yeah.
爹地
Daddy?
伊凡  我去...
Evan! What the...
你是怎么把门打开的
You're opening doors now? How did...
-我刚才看到怪物了  -什么
- I saw a monster. - A what?
把你的手指插到我屁眼里
Stick your finger in my asshole.
对  操我  操我
Fuck, yeah! Fuck, yeah!
来吧  来吧  操我  狠狠地操我
Come on, come on, come on. Fuck, yeah!
快射我一...
I want you to cum all over my...
哦  天哪
Oh, my God!
伊凡不要碰那个
Evan, don't touch that!
不要
Don't...
爹地  出血了
Daddy, boo-boo.
我去啊
What the...
天啊
Oh, my God.
别动  在这呆着
Okay, don't move. Stay here.
爹地需要创可贴
Daddy needs a Band-Aid.
米雪
Michelle?
你这是在
Do you...
妈咪  爹地  你们还好吗
Mommy, Daddy, are you okay?
美国派4
美国重逢
你婚姻中的性爱是否已变得千篇一律
吉姆?莱文斯汀
Jim Levenstein.
他们还没给你配个助理是吧
They still haven't gotten you an assistant yet, huh?
凯文  抱歉  我本想给你回电话的
Kev, I'm sorry, I've been meaning to call you back.
-我有点…  -忙吗
- I've just been... -Busy?
明白
I get it.
那我快点说  好吧
Look, I'll make this quick, okay?
那个重聚  你参加吗
The reunion, you in?
真要有聚会吗
Hold on, is that really happening?
是的  伙计  上你的脸书看看
Yeah, man, check your Facebook.
虽然十周年庆已经过去了两三年
Look, I know they missed the ten-year by a couple,
但是大伙还是很有兴趣参加
but, you know, seems like people are actually going.
你好啊  宝贝
Hey, Hon.
晚餐闻起来很棒
Dinner smells great.
你好  艾丽
Hey, Ellie.
你好  吉姆
Hey, Jim.
全美收视冠军真人秀
待会看"单身女郎"大结局
Ooh, Bachelorette finale later.
知名真人秀
别忘了  我们还要看"家庭主妇"
And don't forget, we still have to watch Real Housewives.
嗯  怎么会忘呢
Yeah, how could I forget?
凯文  你知道我最喜欢的主妇是谁吗
Hey, Kev, you know who my favorite housewife is?
你
You.
很有趣
Very funny.
我爱我老婆
Look, I love my wife,
但是我需要一个周末跟大家聚聚
but I need a weekend with the guys.
我们会早去几天  这次没有硬条
Come on, we'll go a few days early. No Stifler this time.
只有你我  奥兹和芬治
Just you, me, Oz and Finch.
行  祝你好运吧
Yeah, well, good luck with that.
据说芬治他妈都不知道他在哪
I heard Finch's mom doesn't even know where he is.
奥兹呢
And what about Oz?
你真的觉得发生了这么多事后
I mean, do you really
他还会来吗
think he would come with all he has going on?
这里是体育大观
And we're back here on Sports View,
今天我的特约嘉宾  查德?欧丘辛柯
with my special guest, Chad Ochocinco.
查德  你觉得在今年的橄榄球球员选秀中
Chad, which college football powerhouse
哪只大学强队能贡献出最多的新秀
is gonna have the most players drafted in this year's draft?
我认为是我的母校
I'm gonna have to go with my alma mater,
也就是俄勒冈州立大学校队
the Oregon State.
得了  伙计  你在开什么玩笑  欧丘
Come on, man! What are you smoking, Ocho?
你觉得我不知道自己在说什么吗
You think I don't know what I'm talking about?
帮个忙  看看带子
Do me a favor, take a look at the tape.
-宝贝  我回来了  -俄州大的球员可是能
- Hey, babe, I'm home! - Oregon State has players
在全场打任何位置的全能球员
on both sides of the ball.
这给我的特约嘉宾查德?欧丘辛柯
And that wraps it up for my special guest,
画上了一个完美的句号
Chad Ochocinco.
我是克里斯?奥斯莱克
This is Chris Ostreicher
提醒你关注运动  那个赛事儿啊
reminding you to play on, playa!
蜜儿  你在哪
Hey, Mia?
天哪  真有趣
Oh, my gosh! So funny.
嗨  宝贝
Oh, hey, baby!
刚才我还在看你的节目
I was just watching your show a minute ago.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
你说呢  你怎么跟别人在浴池泡澡
You tell me. You're in the hot tub with another dude.
你在担心德尚吗
You are worried about Deshaun?
太好玩了
Aw, that is so cute!
德尚就是我跟你说的室内设计师
Deshaun's the interior decorator I told you about.
嗨  克里斯托弗
Hey, Christopher!
把衣服脱了  跟我们一起泡
Strip down! Come join us.
或许下次吧  德尚
Maybe next time, Deshaun.
我还是不明白为什么需要一个室内设计师
I still don't get why we need an interior decorator.
"造型"杂志要过来拍照  所以得弄的漂亮点
Because the place needs to look perfect for the In Style shoot.
宝贝  相信我
Babe, trust me.
还记得你一开始不想参加"热舞明星"的事吗
Remember how you didn't wanna go on Celebrity Dance Off at first?
现在想想你那么多的粉丝
Now think of all the fans you have.
差点忘了
Oh! I almost forgot,
马里奥?洛佩兹要开一个纪念日派对
Mario Lopez is having a Memorial Day party.
我跟他说我们参加
I told him we're in.
其实那个周末我想参加
Actually, I was thinking about going
我们高中同学的聚会
to my high school reunion that weekend.
好吧  如果你去  那我也去
Well, if you're going, I'm going, too.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
好
All right.
蜜儿  亲爱的  茹玛的电话
Mia, love, phone call. It's Rumer.
该死  我来跟她说
Oh, shit, let me talk to her.
你怎么总是抄袭我的风格  婊子
What's with you jacking my style, bitch?
克里斯托弗  想来点什么吗
Anything I can get for you, Christopher?
同事们  二逼们  大家早上好
Morning, co-workers and cock-jerkers!
雷吉  给我一点爱吧
Reggie, give me some love.
硬条  你看起来不错
Looking good, Stifler.
女士们  好好工作吧
Ladies, better be working hard,
雇你们来  可不是因为你们脸蛋漂亮
you weren't hired for your looks.
其实  就是因为你们漂亮的脸蛋
Actually, you were.
不是说你
Not you.
搞什么鬼
Seriously?
鲍勃  你还在这干嘛
Bob, what are you doing here?
他们不是把你炒了吗
Don't you know they fired your ass?
什么
What?
我在跟你闹着玩呢
I'm just fucking with you.
不过这也难说
Or am I?
想来杯咖啡吗  美女
Coffee for the pretty lady?
哦  谢谢
Sure, thanks.
要加"伴侣"的话记得告诉我一声
Let me know if you want some creamer with that.
嗨  你还好吗
Hello, you. How are you?
哦  我很好  大屌硬条
Oh, I'm good, Stifmeister,
知道为什么吗  你是最棒的
cause you know what? Cause you're the best.
-对  我是最棒的  -对  你是
- Oh, I am the best. - Yes, you are the...
我可爱死你了
You know, I love you so much.
我下面要爽爽了
That I'm going to just have some fun down here.
-你他妈在干什么  -天哪
- What the hell are you doing? - Jesus Christ!
该死  对不起  度莱斯瓦米先生
Shit, sorry, Mr. Duraiswamy.
我只是...
It's... I was just...
好了  物归原位
That's good, it's all clean.
我吩咐过你打印出早上的报表
I told you to print out
放在我的桌子上
the morning numbers and put them on my desk,
你却把这当你家了啊
and you're making yourself at home?
-不  我只是想  -"我只是想"
- No, I just thought... - "I just thought..."
我付钱不是请你来空想的  你只是个临时工
I don't pay you to think. You are a temp.
关于那个  我觉得我被大材小用了
Yeah, about that. I feel like I'm being way underutilized here.
这就是你的想法  是吗
Oh, you do, do you?
多谢你告诉我你是怎么想的
Thank you for telling me how you feel.
你不介意听我说我是怎么想的吧
Do you mind if I tell you how I feel?
我觉得越早你认识到自己是个奴才
I feel the sooner you realize that you're the bitch,
而不是主子
not the boss,
你日子就能过得越好
the better off you will be.
-傻逼  -你说什么
- Fucker. - What was that?
没什么
Nothing!
没什么  度莱斯瓦米先生
Nothing, Mr. Duraiswamy.
傻逼
Fucker!
欢迎来到东大瀑布镇
我们还没谈谈
You know, we still haven't discussed the whole
浴缸事件
bathtub incident.
那个啊  那个...
Oh, that? That's...
那个  不用担心
That... Don't worry about that.
我意思是  很明显
Well, I mean, you know, obviously,
我很希望我是那个
I would prefer it if I was the one
能让你性奋的人  但是...
that made you feel that way, but...
我知道的你的感受
I know how you feel.
每次我要网购  搜索"亚马逊"的时候
Every time I want to shop online and I start typing "Amazon,"
一个叫"劲爆大学骚货"的网址就弹了出来
"Amazingcollegesluts.Com" Pops up.
"劲爆"什么
Amazing what?
好吧  很明显
Okay, look, obviously
我们两个是应该多找些乐子
we need to have more fun together.
我保证  就这个周末
I promise you, this weekend,
会有很多二人时光  好吗
there is going to be plenty of Jim and Michelle time, okay?
你好  甜心
Hello, sweetheart.
最近好吗
How are you?
-很高兴见到你  -你好  爸爸
- It's so good to see you. -Hey, Dad.
你好啊儿子  过来抱一个
Hello, son! Come here.
看看  这是谁啊
Oh, no! Look who that is!
瞧这壮小伙啊
Look at this big bruiser! Oh, my goodness!
-他长大了  -看看他啊
- He has grown. - Look at him! Huh?
还穿着尿不湿呢
Someone's got a little poopy diaper.
吉姆
Jim?
真不敢相信是你
I can't believe it's you.
不记得我了吧  是不是
You don't remember me, do you?
还记得天线宝宝周二会吗
Uh... Remember Teletubby Tuesdays?
凯菈
Kara?
天哪
Oh, my God.
啊  你都长这么大了
What? You're not a kid anymore.
我早就不是小孩子了
It's been a long time since I needed a babysitter.
真不敢相信你都长这么大了
I can't believe how much you've grown up.
谢谢
Thanks!
实际上明天就是我十八岁生日了
It's actually my 18th birthday tomorrow.
都快十八了啊
Eighteen, wow.
你应该来我的派对
You should come to my party.
谢谢你  但是可能有点困难
Thank you, no. I... Yeah, that might be difficult.
求你了  我很想你能来
Please, I want you to come so bad.
凯菈  我们得走了
Hey, Kara! We gotta go.
好吧  放松
Okay, relax.
那个是AJ  别管他
That's AJ. Don't ask.
希望明天可以见到你
Hopefully I will see you tomorrow.
那人他妈的是谁
Who the fuck was that?
甜心
Hey, sweetie.
你在跟谁说话
Who were you talking to?
邻家的小孩子
That was just the kid next door.
你好  我的老朋友
Hello, my old friends.
我差点没把它们扔了
I thought about throwing them out,
但是它们的情感价值太重了
but they just have too much sentimental value.
是啊
Yeah.
哦  吉姆  吉姆  吉姆
Oh, Jim, Jim, Jim.
我还记得你孩子时候的样子
You know, I can remember when you were just a little guy.
现在你都有自己的孩子了
And now you've got your own little guy.
我知道
I know.
你都还没发觉  他很快就长成青少年了
And before you know it, he's gonna be a teenager...
你会教他怎么手淫
And you'll be teaching him about masturbation
还有那些关于小家伙鸡鸡
and, you know, all the do's and all the don'ts
能做的和不能做的
that have to do with the little guy's weenie.
对吧
Okay. Right?
希望他到了青少年的年纪
Hopefully, it'll be more
他的小香肠能大一些
of a bratwurst by the time he's a teenager...
好吧  爸爸  我明白  但是...
Okay, Dad, I get it. ...but I'm just...
你总得面对这些事情
Well, these are things you're gonna have to deal with.
我明白  只是现在有点早  他才两岁
I understand. It's just, you know, he's two.
对  或许还早  但是
Well, yeah, maybe you've got time, but...
我只是  不想再谈论他的小鸡鸡
So, you know, I just, I'd rather not talk about his penis.
-最近好吗  爸爸  -我很好
- How you doing, Dad? - I'm good.
有什么娱乐活动  最近有看什么电影吗
Yeah? What are you doing for fun? You seen any movies lately?
是的  我过去常和你妈一起看电影
Well, you know, your mother and I did go to a lot of movies.
妈妈都过世三年了
You know, it has been three years since she passed, Dad.
在镇子里  总能找个能陪你看电影的人吧
There's gotta be someone in town you can see a movie with.
现在不是有你了吗
I have you now.
我们今晚去看电影  你和我
We'll see a movie tonight, you and me.
今晚吗
Tonight?
我和那些老朋友有约
Well, I made plans with the guys,
晚上在酒吧见
to meet up with them tonight at the bar...
-但是...  -也是  也是
- But... - Yeah, yeah...
但我没必要今天就去  明天也可以
But I don't need to do that. I can do that tomorrow.
别  别  你就是为了聚会回来的  是吧
No. No, no, no, no. This is why you're in town, isn't it?
没事  你去吧  我没事的
No, no, no. You go. I'll be fine.
我打算今晚待在家里
I was just planning on staying in tonight
做一些阅读的工作
and, you know, doing a little reading.
不是看这个  当然不是
Oh, not this. No. No.
不过  我还记得里面有篇很有趣的文章
Although, I do remember reading a very interesting article
带有巴西风情的
on something Brazilian.
这几张怎么粘在一起了
Boy, these pages are all stuck together here.
给我吧
I got it.
凯文
Kev.
吉姆  还好吧
What's up, man? Jim.
嗨  伙计们
Hey, guys!
奥兹  他在这
Oz. There he is.
你终于来了
You made it.
我错过了你的婚礼
Hey, I missed your wedding;
但是我绝对不会错过这个
I wasn't gonna miss this.
嗨  伙计  怎么样
Hey, buddy. What's up, pal?
很高兴见到你
Good to see you. Yeah, man.
嗨  凯文
Hey, Kev!
看起来很不错啊  看看你这一身
Looking good, look at you!
得了吧
Oh, stop it. Come on.
先生们
Gentlemen.
-是你吗芬治  -真的是他
- Finch? - Finch!
天哪  见到你太好了  詹姆斯
Oh, my God! It great to see you, James.
完全变样了啊  吉姆
Changed at all, Jim.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you, pal.
我以为你来不了呢
I didn't think you were gonna make it.
芬治  近来怎么样
Finch, how are you, man?
在北京惹了点麻烦后  我就去了迪拜
So, after my troubles in Beijing, I just moved to Dubai,
然后就沉迷于
and then I got all caught
地下赌牌
up in the world of underground baccarat.
然后跟这个非洲部落度过了剩下的零九年
Spent the rest of 09 living with this African tribe.
他们还让我当了他们的荣誉族人
Oh, they made me an honorary tribesman.
看起来很痛的样子
Whoa, that looks like it hurt.
看上去痛是因为它确实很痛  凯文
It looks like that because it did hurt, Kevin.
然后就一直骑自行车环游南美
Since then, I've just been biking through South America.
你估计是这世界上最有意思的人了吧
So, basically, you are the most interesting man in the world.
-是啊  -我猜猜
- Yeah. - Let me guess,
你们来这里重聚是吧
you guys are here for the reunion, huh?
猜对了 99级学生
You got it. Class of 99.
我之前是不是见过你
Haven't I seen you before?
对  我是电视主持
Yeah, I'm on TV.
不  不是你  是你
No, not you. You.
你的脸  很熟悉
'Cause, your face, you're just so familiar.
对了  这是你  是吧
Yeah! Yeah, this is you, right?
-我的天  -是娜迪亚
- Oh, Man! - Nadia!
更多  更多  你这坏小伙
More, more, you bad boy!
我发誓我把它们都弄下来了  你是怎么
I swear I had these all taken down. How did you...
对了  你早泄了几次来着
Oh, yeah. How many times did you pre-ejaculate again?
放了他吧
Oh, leave him alone.
我打赌你们那时候都还是饥渴的处男
I bet you were all desperate virgins back then.
塞琳娜?维嘉
Selena Vega.
-塞琳娜?维嘉就站在我们面前  -等等  塞琳娜
- That's Selena Vega in front of us. - Wait, wait, wait, Selena...
你是米雪乐队里的那个朋友
Hold on, Michelle's friend from band?
你猜对了
You got it.
天哪  很抱歉没认出你来
Oh, my God. I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
你看起来  大不一样了
You look... different.
下一轮我请  好吗  伙计们
Well, next round's on me, okay, guys?
这妞原来竟是乐团的
Hey, that chick was in band?
听我说  我这么长时间来
Look, this is the first long weekend
好不容易能有个双休日
I have had in a while,
所以一秒都不能浪费
so I wanna make it count.
我要家里一尘不染  酒池肉林
I want the place spotless, and I want it filled with booze.
我要你周日晚上把房子腾出来
And I wanna make sure you're not around on Sunday night,
因为我要带些重聚的老伙计回来
'cause I plan on bringing some ass back from the reunion,
我希望你到时候  别在那添乱  明白了吗
and I wanna tap that without you there. You got it?
斯蒂文  第一点  这是我的房子
You know, first of all, Steven, it's my house.
我还让你住在这  是你小子走运
You're lucky I'm letting you stay here.
你让我找个工作  我不是找了吗
Look, you wanted me to get a job, so I got one.
至少让我周末好好聚聚吧
At least let me have the house for the weekend.
我的房子  我做主
My house, my rules.
至于今晚  如果你不想回家后
And as for tonight, if you don't wanna risk coming home
看到什么不该看到的事
and seeing more of your mother than you'd like,
我建议你还是晚点回来吧
I suggest you stay out late.
真恶心
Gross.
这真是...
That was really...
酒保妹  来杯百威
Hey, bar wench, can I get a Budweiser?
干杯
Beer down.
你们这帮贱人在这干嘛
What the fuck are you fuckers doing here?
-你也来了  -来什么
- You made it! - Made what?
你们在说什么
What are you talking about?
你什么意思  我们发了邮件给你
What do you mean? We sent you an e-mail
在聚会之前的一两天先聚一下
about getting together a couple of days before the reunion.
我肯定是在大屌硬条这个词里打了两个"F"
You know what? I must have put two F's in "Stifmeister."
-什么  -很抱歉
- What? - I'm sorry.
两个F  你这傻逼
Two F's? You dumb-ass!
凯文
Kev!
凯文  你脸上长的是阴门吗
Hey, Kevin, is that a pussy on your face?
得了
Oh, come on!
正点
Nice.
硬条  看起来不错啊
So, Stifler, you're looking sharp.
最近在哪风光
What are you up to these days?
我在JBH环球公司上班
I work at JBH Global.
这可是大公司啊
Wow! That's a big-time firm.
具体是什么职位
What do you do over there?
你知道的
Oh, you know,
就是投资一类的东西
investment stuff.
难怪我们的金融系统崩溃了
People wonder why our financial system's falling apart.
围巾不错  你终于出柜了
Nice scarf. I see you finally came out of the closet.
硬条  你老妈还好吧
How is your mother, Stifler?
你这狗屎  离我妈远点
You stay away from my mom, shitbreak.
好了 过去的都过去了
Okay, boys, the past is the past.
先和解好吗
We can bury the hatchet here, huh?
是啊  去他的
Yeah, fuck it.
热裤妹  给我们所有人来一轮野格炸弹
Hey, short-shorts! A round of J?gerbombs for me and my boys!
去你妈的  硬条
Go fuck yourself, Stifler.
她怎么知道我名字
How the hell does she know my name?
肘子妞
Lard Arms?
天哪  硬条
Jesus, Stifler.
我们在谈一个丑小鸭变白天鹅的事  是吗
Talk about an ugly duckling turning into a swan, right?
让我看看
Let me see that.
从前揉过她的道
Oh! Fingered her,
这个是毛乳头  这个是奶子大
hairy nips, huge boobs.
找到她了
There she is!
我老二尝过的极品美味
The crème de my cock.
吹箫皇后小莱
Blowjob Lipstein.
硬条  人家本名是萝妮
Her given name was Loni, Stifler.
她原来总叫我大硬条
She used to call me Big Stiffy.
那可真是一张叫我魂牵梦萦的嘴啊
She was the mouth that got away.
最后一轮
Last call!
这么快  伙计们等着
Already? Wait here, guys.
看看这个  高中愿望单
Oh! Man, the Senior Wish List.
你觉得自己的未来是什么样的
愿望单  我不记得这东西了
Wish List? I don't remember that.
那可是年鉴里俗气的一页
Oh, yeah, man. It's that cheesy page in the yearbook
我们在那上面书写了对未来的愿望
where we all had to write wishes about our future.
是吗  我来瞧瞧  你写了什么俗气的东西
What, did you write something cheesy? Let's see.
克里斯?奥斯莱克
"Chris Ostreicher.
希望成为他儿子的曲棍球队教练
Hopes to coach his son's lacrosse team."
这不是很甜蜜吗
Oh! Isn't that the sweetest thing?
好吧
Well,
我猜我当时想着到现在应该有家庭了
I guess I thought I'd have a family by now.
想听听你写了些什么吗  芬治
All right, you wanna hear what you wrote, Finch?
当然
I do.
保罗?芬治希望找到"le grand amour"
"Paul Finch hopes to find le grand amour."
没错  真爱
Yes, true love.
然而我连你们所谓的稳定关系都还没找到
Alas, I have yet to find what you would call a real relationship.
对  毕竟上硬条的老妈不算
Right, because banging Stifler's mom didn't count.
凯文  来看看你写了什么
All right, let's see what you got, Kev.
凯文?迈尔斯希望可以和
"Kevin Myers. Hopes to still be living it up
迷人的碧琪?兰森天长地久
with the amazing Vicky Lathum."
-天哪  -碧琪  真的假的
- Oh, man! - Vicky! What?
我肯定你老婆听到这个会很高兴
I am sure your wife would be very happy to read that.
什么呀  我那时候正在和碧琪约会
What? I was dating Vicky at the time.
我看看我写了什么
Let me see what I put.
吉姆?莱文斯汀
"Jim Levenstein
希望能过着里奇?马丁式的性爱生活"
Hopes to have the sex life of Ricky Martin."
我猜你当年还不知道他是基佬吧
So, I'm assuming you didn't know he was gay back then.
吉姆  多亏你找了个
Jim, it's a good thing you found a woman
性欲旺盛的女人
with the sex drive of a dozen groupies. Hmm?
我想你做的爱  比我们都多
I mean, you're probably having more sex than any of us.
这种事哪有准头
Probably, you know.
希望你们都渴了  硬条大爷我来了
Hope you guys are thirsty. Stifler Claus is here.
硬条  你不觉得这有点多了吗
Whoa! Stifler, that's a little too much, don't you think?
伙计  爷们点  放胆喝
Dude, find your balls and return them to your sack.
要我说  派对继续
I say we keep this party going.
这个周末我们要无法无天
I say we make this weekend our bitch.
我们可以一起聚会
We could party together,
干过去一起干过的那些疯事
do all the same shit that we used to do together.
一切都将是昨日重现
It'll be just like old times.
没错  我就是为了这个来的
Hell yes! That's why I'm here.
没有"单身女郎"  没有"家庭主妇"
No Bachelorette, no Real Housewives.
十三年的重聚仅此一次
Thing is, you only get one chance at your 13th reunion.
老实说  我有点想回去跟我老婆甜蜜一下
I was kind of hoping to spend a little time with the wife.
-操  -伙计
- Fuck! - Dude!
-詹姆斯  -行了吧你
- James? - What? Come on!
好吧  我加入  我当然加入  什么大不了的
I mean, I'm in. Of course I'm in. Come on, what?
那么各位  我希望你们的套子都戴好了
Then, gentlemen, I hope you're all wearing protection,
因为这个周末  我们要疯他个天昏地暗
because this weekend, we're gonna fuck shit up!
-干杯  -干了
- Cheers! - Yeah! All right!
怎么回事
What the fuck?
该死
Holy shit.
怎么回事
What happened?
我记不大清了
I don't really remember.
都怪你  你昨晚让他喝了多少
I blame you. How much did you let him drink last night?
实话说  没多少
Honestly, not that much.
我们去湖滨之前得收拾好这些东西
Well, we gotta clean this up before we go to the lake.
什么  去湖滨?
What? The lake?
对  去湖滨  这可是你的主意
Yeah, the lake, dude. It was your idea.
昨晚我们一直在商量这事
We discussed all this last night.
没错没错  是去湖边
Oh, the lake! Yes, of course, the...
吉姆  能把纸巾拿给我吗
Hey, Jim, can you hand me those paper towels, please?
-那些纸巾吗  -没错
- Oh, those paper towels? - The paper ones.
快拿纸巾来  吉姆
The paper towels, Jim.
-吉姆  -好的好的
- Jim! - Yeah...
快去拿纸巾
The paper towels!
十分抱歉
I'm really sorry.
吉姆  你应该知道那个锅盖是透明的吧
Jim, you do realize that the lid is see-through, right?
好眼力
Good eye.
这就是孩子他爹
That's the father of my child.
干什么呢
Oh, come on!
-注意点  -算了  就这样吧
- Hey, watch it! - Okay, jeez.
是我的错觉
Am I wrong, or was this
还是这里没我们年轻时那么有趣了
place a lot more fun when we were younger?
不  我觉得没变  只是我们老了而已
No, no. I think it's the same. We're just old now.
但是我们那时候也像这些小孩一样烦人吗
But were we just as obnoxious as these kids back in the day?
绝对不是
No.
我们这一代人比较成熟
Us, our generation, we were more mature.
伙计们  看我的
Hey, guys, check it out.
猎鲍鲨
Vagina shark!
他乱摸我
He touched my snatch!
我收回刚才的话
I take that back.
天啊
Oh, my God.
哥们  你们非得这么盯着不可吗
Fellas, do you gotta stare?
-没错  -当然了
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我们当然得一直盯着
Yes, we do need to stare.
吉姆还敢再明目张胆一点吗
Could Jim be any more obvious?
让他放松一下吧
Oh, give him a break.
我是说  你不是每天
I mean, it's not every day you
都能看见活生生的模特的
get to see a model walking around off the page.
最近在莱文斯汀家
There hasn't been a whole lot of sexy time
性生活可不大和谐
in the Levenstein household lately.
怎么回事
Why not?
不知道  我现在当妈妈了
I don't know. I'm a mom now.
拜托
Oh, please!
你当妈妈可不意味着
Just because you're a mom doesn't mean
你的那一面就被抹杀了
there isn't a whole other side to you.
还记得有次在乐队营那会
Hey, remember that one time at band camp
我们互相舔对方身上的奶油...
when we licked whipped cream off each other's...
是是是  我记得
Yes! Yes! I remember.
但是过去的事就让它过去  行不行
Let's keep that in the past, though, okay?
她居然...
Oh, she's...
没错  你确实该这么做
Yeah, well, you gotta do that
要不然身上就要被晒出斑马纹了
or else you're gonna get tan lines.
侧胸  在那  抱歉  奥兹  快看
Sideboob. There... Sorry. Sideboob. Ozzy, look!
好了  少出洋相了
Okay! Come on!
你可真走运  奥兹
You're a lucky man, Oz.
得了吧几位  我觉得我们都非常的
Oh, come on, guys. I think we're all pretty
幸运
lucky.
等等  那是海瑟吗
Wait, is that Heather?
就是她
Yeah, it is.
海瑟
Heather.
克里斯
Chris!
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
可能是我们想到一块了
I guess we had the same idea, huh?
克里斯  这是朗  我的男朋友
Chris, this is Ron, my boyfriend.
克里斯?奥斯莱克  我是朗?道格拉斯
Chris Ostreicher, Ron Douglas.
很荣幸认识你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
你好
How do you do?
朗是我们医院的心脏病医师
Ron's a cardiologist at my hospital.
心脏病医师  真酷
A cardiologist. Wow.
没错  不过听着
Yeah. And, hey, listen, my
我朋友都叫我朗医生  朗生或者德朗
friends call me Doctor Ron, D-Ron or just Dron.
所以你怎么叫我都行
So you feel free.
好的
Okay.
你好  大便脸
Hey, fuckface!
唱诗班的妞  你也来了
Choir chick! Whoa!
很高兴见到你  硬条
Nice to see you, too, Stifler.
这傻冒是谁
Who's this douche?
我是她的男朋友
I'm her boyfriend.
也就是说  你们俩现在操得欢
So, you two are banging,
而你们俩从前一起操
and you two used to bang.
对你们所有人都挺难堪的吧
This must be awkward for all of you.
你来了以后确实如此了
It is now.
那个小杂种把我的胸罩抢走了
That little shit took my top!
还回来
Give it back!
那是我的女朋友
That's my girlfriend.
这是什么  这又是什么
What's this? What's this?
臭小子  你以为你在干什么
Hey, kid! What do you think you're doing?
快快快  快走
Hey! Come on, come on, let's go!
够了  伙计们  这可不好
Come on, guys. Not cool!
你们这帮蠢货又能怎么样
What're you assholes gonna do about it?
这下有趣了
Well, that was interesting.
我们是不是应该做点什么
Well, should we do something?
有什么好做的呢  拜托
What are we gonna do? Come on.
同意  没必要自贬身份跟他们较劲
Agreed. There's no need to stoop to their level.
混账东西
Fuck that!
我知道他们去哪
I know exactly where they're going.
硬条?
Stifler?
他窜哪去了
Where the hell is he?
伙计们  这太蠢了
Guys, this is stupid.
我真的不能让米雪一等再等
I really can't keep Michelle waiting.
我们能掉头回去吗
Can we just head back?
等会  等硬条忙完
Hold on. Let Stifler do his thing.
我就担心这一茬
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
你们看到那帮家伙的表情了吗
Did you guys see the look on their faces?
太他妈帅了
Fucking awesome.
他疯了
He is crazy.
我觉得那里有一个人原来是凯菈的保姆
I think one of those guys was Kara's babysitter.
哪一个
Which one?
长得像亚当?桑德勒的那个
You know, the one that looked like Adam Sandier.
硬条最好别干什么出格的事
Stifler better not do anything crazy.
他就是想吼那些臭小子们几句
All he's gonna do is tell them off.
他不是要把他们的摩托艇放跑吗
I thought he was gonna cut their jet skis free.
那往他们的防晒霜里撒尿的事呢
What happened to pissing in their suntan lotion?
等下  他告诉我的是去偷他们的啤酒
Hold on. He told me he was going to steal their beer.
硬条
Stifler.
瞧  他来了
Oh, wait. There he is.
很好
All right.
没错  他在拿他们的啤酒
Yep, he's taking their beer.
快点  硬条  速战速决
All right, hurry up, Stifler. Come on.
他在干什么
What is he doing?
-不不不  完蛋了  -等等
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. - Wait.
-天啊  -我的天
- Oh, God! - Oh, my God.
斯蒂文  别这样
Steven! No!
天啊
Oh, God.
你真的确定凯菈今晚让你开苞吗
Yo, so you really think Kara's gonna give it up tonight?
她就等着十八岁这一天  你扳指头数数
She was waiting until she turns 18. You do the math.
我的指头也就能数出来的
The only math I know is
就是你跟她一次都没睡过
you've added your penis to her vagina zero times.
詹妮弗可不是烂货
Jennifer's not a skank.
老兄  她确实是
Dude, yes, she is.
我得吐一会
I'm gonna throw up.
天啊  太恶心了
Oh, my God. That's disgusting.
你在干什么
What're you doing?
爷在拉屎
I'm taking a shit!
快点  赶紧的
Hurry up. Come on!
来一口干  干了  干了
Down it, man! Just chug it! Chug it!
干掉它  别翻过去了
Do it. Do it! Don't puss out.
别翻倒了
Don't puss out!
撤退  快撤退
Let's just go. Let's go.
快快快快
Go, go. Go, go, go, go. Go, go.
再来一瓶吗
You want another?
必须的
For sure.
哥们  我告诉你们
Guys, I'm telling you
她今晚就要实现一年前的诺言了
tonight is gonna be the night she promised me a year ago.
这他妈...
What the...
傻逼
Hey! Dipshit!
不要
No!
不要  不要
No, no!
硬条  你脑子烧坏了吗
Stifler! Are you crazy?
天啊  硬条  不是说好只偷他们的啤酒吗
Jesus, Stifler, what happened to just stealing their beer?
我知道  但这样更绝  不是吗
I know, this is so much better, right?
什么
What?
你把他们的摩托艇都毁了
You destroyed their jet skis.
谁让他们溅我们一身水
They splashed us.
所以呢...
So...
拜托  伙计们  这么干多有意思
Come on, guys. That was pretty funny.
也许高中时代挺有趣的  现在这可是重罪
Maybe in high school it was funny. Now it's just a felony.
除非我们被抓了
Only if we get caught.
没错  你确实得承认
Yeah, you gotta admit
给那些臭小子们点教训也不错
it was nice giving those kids a little payback.
让他们懂得尊敬前辈对他们有好处
Maybe it was good that they will learn to respect their elders.
太对了
Exactly!
等我一会  我要去找点卫生纸
Hey, give me a second, I gotta find some toilet paper.
真恶心
That's gross.
都还好吗  99级同学们
What's up, Class of '99-ers?
天啊  碧琪
Oh, my God! Vicky!
难以置信你也来了
I can't believe you're here.
我昨晚从纽约飞过来的
Yeah, I flew in from New York last night.
我本来在陪父母出游
I've been hanging out with my parents.
之前他们还说起你了
They were actually just talking about you earlier.
真的吗  都说什么了
Really? About what?
说他们发现我们在瀑布旁边亲热那会
That time they caught us making out at the Falls.
没错
Oh, right.
瀑布那啊  感觉都是上辈子的事了
The Falls. Wow, I haven't been there in forever.
米雪原来也喜欢去瀑布
Michelle used to love going to the Falls.
那地方简直是浪漫的化身
The place is romance incarnate.
太对了  我第一次舔肛就是在瀑布旁
Hell, yeah. I got my first rim job at the Falls.
好吧
Okay.
亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
Mmm, sweetie pie!
一天没见了
Hello.
那些人都想去瀑布玩
So, the guys were all talking about heading over to the Falls.
那我们的二人时间怎么办
Well, what about Jim and Michelle time?
我就是觉得那边比较浪漫
I was thinking it could be kind of romantic.
我也想去  但是你爸爸陪小伊一整天了
Well, I'd love to, but your dad has been with Ev all day.
你说的没错
Yeah, no, you're right.
好吧  我们回家好了
Okay. Yeah, we'll just, we'll go home.
不用  你去玩吧
Oh, no, no. You go and have fun.
-真的吗  -当然了
- Really? - Yeah.
只是你回家的时候一定要做好准备
Just, when you get home, you just better be ready.
应该是你一定要做好准备
You better be ready.
我早就准备好了
I'm ready.
硬条  你还找得到北吗
Um, Stifler, do you know where you're going?
我对这里了如指掌
I know this place like the back of my cock.
像是个高中生派对
It looks like a high school party.
全是高中妞
With high school chicks.
场面真火爆
It's on.
小心点  硬条
Watch it, Stifler.
这些姑娘年龄差不多只有你一半大
You know these girls are, like, half your age.
我知道
I know.
是我的错觉  还是现在的姑娘比从前淫荡了
Okay, is it just me, or do girls today seem a bit sluttier?
你的感觉很准
Definitely.
青少年性行为  彩虹派对  互发裸照
Teen sex, rainbow parties, sexting nude photos...
Kathie Lee & Hoda上这些东西应有尽有
I saw it all on Kathie Lee & Hoda.
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
吉姆?
Jim?
-凯菈  -你来了
- Kara. - You came!
失陪
Sorry.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
老天  这就是你小时候的保姆吗
Oh, my God, is this the babysitter?
听起来你好像把我塑造成超级英雄了
You make it sound like I'm a superhero.
比跑车还快  比面包车还要猛
Faster than a speeding stroller, more powerful than a mini-van.
我说过他很有趣
I told you he was funny.
真可爱
He's adorable.
吉姆  要不要给你的朋友引荐一下我
Hey, Jim. Do you wanna introduce me to your friends?
坚决不
No.
姑娘们  这是硬条
Girls, this is Stifler.
那么你们怎么认识我最好的朋友吉姆的
So, how do you know my best friend Jim?
吉姆在我小时候照顾过我
Jim used to be my babysitter.
我正好要来杯庆生酒
Hey, I was just gonna do a birthday shot.
能陪我喝一杯吗
Do you guys wanna do one with me?
不不不  算了吧
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
当然可以  当然可以
Yeah. Oh, yes, yes, yes.
-我不该喝  -咱该喝  该喝
- I shouldn't. - Yes, we should, yes, we should.
我从没在公共场合做过爱
Never have I ever had sex in public.
真的吗  也就是说你们都没做过吗
Really? None of you?
拜托  海瑟  你一滴酒都没喝
Oh, come on, Heather. You haven't drunk once.
你也太正经了
You are such a prude!
或者是因为我没在公共场合做过爱
Or maybe I've just never had sex in public.
好吧  我从来没群交过
Okay, never have I ever been in an orgy.
其实那些人都很好
They were really nice guys.
信不信由你  这是我第一次参加高中生派对
Believe it or not, this is my first high school party.
你也没错过什么好东西
You didn't miss much.
我总喜欢待在家里听听广播
I always preferred staying at home, throwing on a little NPR.
你比我酷多了
You were so much cooler than me.
我就是随便写写《X档案》同人小说
I sat around writing X-Files fan fiction.
我曾把《卡拉马佐夫兄弟》翻译成拉丁文玩
I translated The Brothers Karamazov into Latin for fun.
太性感了
That is so sexy.
还是你识货
You know it is.
近几年我就是干干建筑师
I've only been working as an architect
而且是窝在家里工作
for the last few years, and from home.
十年间你都没换过公司
You've been with the same company for over ten years.
真了不起  我觉得你的人生十分顺利
That's awesome, it sounds like everything is working out for you.
是的  我是说真的挺顺  尤其是工作方面
Yeah. I mean, everything's good, especially work-wise.
但是现在我们回这个镇里
But now that we're back here in the town
见了见老朋友
and we see, like, all of our old friends
结果大家都结婚生子
and everyone's married and having kids
我就有了点想法
it just makes me, you know, think.
你还好吧  凯文
You okay there, Kev?
没事  我只是一般不这么喝酒
Yeah, I just don't normally drink like this.
你是说在迈尔斯家庭酒会的时候
You're telling me you haven't gotten a little bit tipsy
你一丁点都没醉吗
on Myers Family Wine Night?
看来有人在偷偷地关注我的脸书主页了
I see somebody's been stalking my Facebook page.
不过至少我从不拍我吃了什么
At least I don't take pictures of my meals.
现在是谁在偷偷关注谁了
Who's stalking who now?
好  我承认去过你的主页一两次
Okay, so I've been by your page maybe once or twice.
你跟一个叫亚历山卓的人约过会吗
You were dating someone named Alessandro?
他真的知道
You know, he does know that
他是可以穿着上衣照相的  是吗
he can take a picture with his shirt on, right?
亚历山卓早是陈年往事了
Alessandro is long gone.
早就结束了  对吧
It's over, huh?
喝完这杯后我就得回家了
Okay, after this drink, I gotta go home.
吉姆
Jim.
这里有一个你原来照顾过的
There's a smoking hot 18-year-old
火辣得冒烟的十八岁的妞
girl over there that you used to babysit.
你就没什么想法吗
And you're not going to do anything about that?
需不需要我提醒你我已经结婚了
Need I remind you that I am married to Michelle?
这才是重点
Exactly.
这些年轻妞
Dude, these young chicks
床上功夫可是了得
they know some crazy shit in the bedroom.
你可以从凯菈那里取其精华
You could take what you learn from Kara,
然后学以致用到米雪身上
bring it home, and apply it to Michelle.
你很在意婚姻的  不是吗  吉姆
You do care about your marriage, don't you, Jim?
你在胡言乱语什么  硬条
What are you talking about, Stifler?
我可不背着妻子偷情
I'm not gonna cheat on my wife!
老天有眼  我可是个父亲
I'm a father for Christ's sakes.
这才是最完美的
Yeah, that's perfect.
慈父形象魅力无穷  继续打这张牌
Yeah, chicks love a father figure. Keep playing that card, dude.
这不是牌不牌的问题  你现实一点
It's not a card, it's the truth.
你们在聊什么呢
What are you guys talking about?
你知道的  就是
Oh, you know... Just...
吉姆只是在说照顾你十分开心
Jim was just saying how much fun he had taking care of you.
姑娘们  咱们让他们单独叙叙旧吧
Hey, ladies, why don't we give them some time to catch up?
好主意  你先请
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, after you.
不必不必  我们应该一起玩
No, that's not necessary. We should all hang out together.
我们为什么不一起  硬条...
Why don't we all... Stifler, just...
操死她
Be her daddy.
硬条  硬条
Stifler? Stifler!
听起来你和蜜儿都挺喜欢尝试新花样
So, sounds like you and Mia have quite an adventurous lifestyle.
有时候玩得也比较过火
Sometimes a little too adventurous.
海瑟就有点保守
Wow. Well, Heather's a bit more on the conservative side.
但是
But, uh...
但是  老实说  克里斯
But, I gotta be honest, Chris,
我自己愿意试试新花样
I could use a little adventure myself.
你想说什么  朗
What are you getting at, Ron?
我只是说我一般不玩换妻游戏
I'm just saying that usually I'm not one for swapping
但是想到你原来就和海瑟在一起
but the fact that you've been
似乎就没什么问题了
with Heather already, kind of makes it okay.
那么你怎么想
So, what do you think?
你觉得她们愿不愿意这么玩
Think they'd be into it?
我开玩笑的  好了  就是随便说说
I'm kidding. Come on, I'm kidding!
老实说  这事我坚决不干
Seriously, I would never do that!
除非你们愿意
Unless you guys wanted to.
你真的到过南美的每个国家吗
So you've really been to every country in South America?
没有全都去
No, no, not all of them.
而且我也不觉得法属圭亚那是个国家
And I don't consider French Guiana a nation.
我记得我那时都等不及要毕业
I remember, I couldn't wait till graduation
那样我就能离开这里脱胎换骨
so I could leave this town and reinvent myself.
你的变化真的不小
You have certainly reinvented yourself.
我也不知道
I don't know.
我灵魂中还是有个微弱的声音
There's just a part of me that still wishes that
希望能探索全世界
I could just explore the world, you know?
能心想事成
Be everything I set out to be.
你可以心想事成  只要动手去干
You can be whoever you wanna be. You just gotta be it.
-想亲热一下吗  -想
- You wanna make out? - Yeah.
你开玩笑吗  我爱死暮光系列了
Are you crazy? I love the Twilight books.
《新月》是我的最爱
New Moon is my favorite.
我也是
Mine, too!
老天  我们真是志同道合
Oh, my God! We have, like, so much in common!
我知道
I know!
想抽一口吗
Wanna hit this?
做梦都想
In more ways than one.
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who this is,
但是我他妈现在真的很忙
but I'm pretty fucking busy right now.
那就抱歉打扰了  殃条
So sorry to interrupt, Stafler.
没想到残奥会晚上还有比赛
Didn't realize the Special Olympics competed at night.
该死
Oh, fuck.
你那边到底怎么回事
What the hell's going on over there?
吃屎噎着了吗
What, are you choking on your own dick?
没事  度莱斯瓦米先生  没事
Nothing, Mr. Duraiswamy, nothing.
有什么需要效劳吗  先生
What can I do for you, sir?
财务处的鲍勃突发心脏病
Bob from Acquisitions had a heart attack.
不知道是哪个混球告诉他被炒了
Some idiot told him that he was fired.
他一下就崩溃了  我也不知道怎么回事
He flipped out, I don't know.
听着  我需要找人完成他的提案
Listen, I need someone to finish his presentation.
我要你周日到公司完成工作  明白吗
I need you to go in on Sunday and get everything ready. Yes?
等等  周日
Oh, wait, Sunday.
我还要参加高中同学聚会呢
I got my high school reunion.
多好玩啊
Oh, wow, how fun!
那行  我给董事长打个电话
Yeah, no, I'll just call the chairman
让他把时间重新安排一下就行了
and I'll get him to reschedule.
真的吗  那太好了
Seriously? Hey, that would be awesome!
我他妈当然是说着玩的  蠢货
That was a fucking joke, you moron.
老天啊  我在做什么
Jesus Christ, what am I doing?
算了  我自己搞定吧
You know what, I am gonna handle this myself.
不不不  听着  度莱斯瓦米先生
No. No, no, no, listen, Mr. Duraiswamy
我能解决  保证完成任务
I can do it, okay? I promise, I'll get it done.
别再闹什么岔子  殃条
Just don't fuck up, Stafler.
我的名字叫硬条
It's Stifler.
二傻  姑娘们...
Dick! Hey, ladies...
-姑娘们呢  -她们早散了
- Ladies? - They bailed, dude.
我靠
Aw, fuck!
凯菈  你今晚怎么回家
Hey, Kara, how are you getting home tonight?
AJ本来是要开车带我回家
AJ was supposed to drive my car back
但他现在都没影
but he hasn't even shown up yet.
拿摩托艇坏了这种破借口搪塞我
Some lame excuse about his jet skis.
你能相信这混球吗
Can you believe that jerk?
你呢
What about you?
你能带我回去吗
Will you take me?
拜托  我们顺路
Come on! We're going to the same place.
而且  如果你让我醉驾回家
Besides, it wouldn't be responsible
那就太不负责任了
to let me drive in this condition.
对吧
Right?
好吧  凯菈
Okay, Kara.
注意  注意安全
Hey! Whoa! Careful! Careful. Yeah.
我爱死这歌了
Oh, my God, I love this song.
确实不错
It's a good one.
难道经典摇滚不是最棒的吗
Isn't classic rock the best?
经典摇滚  这是经典摇滚吗
Classic rock? This is classic rock now?
凯菈  你该多喝点水
Hey, you know, Kara, you should drink some more water.
我给你的瓶子呢
Where's that bottle I gave you?
-在这呢  -行
- Oh, it's right here. - Okay.
在后座
In the back.
该死  抱歉  刚才有个...
Shit. Sorry. Sorry. There was a...
刚才路上有只小松鼠
There was a little baby squirrel in the road, so...
那可不是水  好了
Whoa! Hey! Whoa! That's not water. Okay.
你喝得可真不少
It's a little too much now.
这么多年过去了
I love how, after all these years,
你还这么照顾我  我就喜欢你这点
you're still taking care of me.
照顾你的工作可没尽头
Well, you know, a babysitter's job never ends.
你知道我一直很喜欢你  是吧
You knew I always had a crush on you, right?
不知道
No.
我想把初夜给你
I want you to be my first.
你的初夜?
Your first?
天啊  好吧
Oh, God. Okay. Um...
凯菈  听着
Kara, listen. Um...
一个人的贞操是十分圣洁的  你知道吗
A person's virginity is something sacred, you know?
你应该留给一个对你有特殊意义的人
You should save yourself for someone special.
你就对我有特殊意义
You're special.
不  我才算不上特殊呢
No! Not special.
你真这么想  我真的...
You think? I really...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
来吧  没人会知道的
Come on. No one will ever find out.
我不知道  我可不认为...
I don't know. I don't think...
我不能这么做
I don't think I should do that.
这太  我不能  我不会
That's... No. I can't. I won't. I won't.
你知道的  这太
So, you know... That's...
你在干嘛  好吧好吧
Whoa! Hello! Okay, okay.
凯菈  凯菈  你不能亲我
Kara, Kara, that's kissing.
凯菈  快停下
Okay, Kara, you need to stop. Stop. Stop!
你觉得我不漂亮吗
You don't think I'm pretty?
没有  你很漂亮凯菈  很漂亮
Oh, no! You're very pretty, Kara. You're very, very...
-真的吗  -真的  很漂亮
- Really? - Yes, very pretty.
-但是我  你很漂亮  -谢谢
- But I... Very pretty. - Thanks.
我的老天
Oh, my God!
该死的  你在干什么
Holy shit! What?
老天  你的衣服呢
Oh, my... Where did your...
来吧
Come on.
我想不到比这更好的生日礼物了
I can't think of a better birthday gift.
我送你一个新苹果手机好不好
What about the new iPhone?
或者小吊坠  还是妮基米娜的新专辑
Huh? Maybe a little pendant? The new Nicki Minaj album?
不好吗  你的胸
No. No? Boobies.
我想要你
I want you!
你不可以  别这样
You can't... Don't do that.
这不好  真的
That's not good, don't...
快停下
Come on, stop.
凯菈  凯菈  停下
Kara! Kara! Stop it.
见鬼
Shit!
见鬼  凯菈
Shit. Kara?
我的老天  凯菈
Holy Jesus! Kara?
凯菈  快醒醒
Kara! Kara! Please wake up, Kara!
快醒醒  凯菈
Kara, wake up. Kara!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我的天
Oh, Jesus, God!
我的天  你还好吗
Oh, my God, are you all right?
吉姆
Jim?
天啊  太疯狂了
What? This is crazy!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我没事  我没事  我只是
Huh? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm okay. I was just...
我刚刚想找什么东西来着
I was reaching for something.
我没事  我很好
Everything's okay. Everything's fine.
我不知道你听说了没
I don't know if you've heard.
你听说了吗
Did you hear?
是我负责这次重聚
I am in charge of the reunion.
噢  没有  这太好了
Oh! Yeah, no, that's... Yeah, that's right.
我想到了一个九十年代主题的计划
Got a whole '90s theme planned.
这还真是
Oh. That's...
我本来请了春巴旺巴乐队
I booked Chumbawamba.
但是那帮混球昨天又取消了
Yeah. But the pricks cancelled yesterday.
我很受打击  但是你了解我的
Was a setback, but you know me,
在哪里倒下我就从哪里爬起来
"I get knocked down but I get up again."
天啊  我明白是咋回事了
Oh, my God! Okay, I see what's going on.
-是米雪吗  -是啊
- Michelle? - Yeah.
正点
Nice.
是啊
Yep.
待会见  伙计
I'll see you later, buddy.
好的  待会见
All right then, I'll see you.
老天  凯菈  快醒醒
Jesus, God. Kara. Kara, wake up.
-我想睡一会  -什么
- I just need a nap. - What?
凯菈  现在不是睡觉的时候  快起来
Kara, this isn't time for a nap. Kara, wake up.
不是睡觉的时候
This isn't napping time.
凯菈  该死
Kara? Shit.
老天  大事不妙了
Oh, God, this is bad. This is very, very bad.
你们怎么这么久才来
What took you guys so long?
我们去找凯文了  他不见了
We were looking for Kevin. Couldn't find him.
而且奥兹那臭小子喝酒喝得不省人事
Plus, that hot piece of ass Oz
所以我们不得不把那小子送回家
is banging got wasted, so we had to drop her off.
你们竟然带他来
You brought him?
他们当然得带上我
Of course they brought me.
你们还在高中忙着打飞机的时候
When you guys were busy jacking off in high school,
我每周末就在练这个
I was running this drill every weekend.
让我看看是怎么回事
Now, let's see what we are dealing with.
我的天啊
Holy shit!
行啊你  吉姆
Way to go, Jim.
啥事都没有  硬条  啥事都没有
Okay, nothing happened, Stifler. Okay? Nothing happened.
别碰她
Stop that!
对不起
I'm sorry.
吉姆  你想怎么办
So, Jim, what do you wanna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我不能把她扔在这
I can't just leave her here naked, you know?
如果警察来了发现这事跟我有关
I mean, if the cops come by and find out I'm involved,
我就完蛋了
I'm screwed.
我们有两个选择
That leaves us with two options.
扔下她或者偷偷送回去
We dump the body or we sneak her inside.
扔下她  我们又不是土匪
Dump the body? This isn't a mob hit.
等一下
Okay, wait a second.
我以前去过她家无数次
I have been in her house a million times to babysit.
我能偷偷地把她从后门送进去
I can totally sneak her in through the back door.
你们得去转移她父母的注意力
I need you guys to distract her parents.
你认为你能搞定吗
Do you think you can do that?
我是专家  吉姆  相信我  交给我吧
I'm an expert, Jim. Trust me. I got this shit.
晚上好先生
Good evening, sir.
我朋友的车抛锚了
My friend's car broke down,
我们在想
and we were just wondering
我们能不能借你的电话叫一下救援
if we could use your phone to call AAA.
你是说你们都没有手机吗
You mean to tell me that none of you have cell phones?
老天  我认得你  你参加过"热舞明星"
Oh, my God, I know you. You were on Celebrity Dance Off.
是的
Oh, yeah!
奥斯莱克
Ostreicher.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
进来吧
Hey, come on in.
你还真是厉害啊  硬条
That was very smooth, Stifler.
闭嘴  蠢货
Shut up, shitbreak.
我上次干这种事的时候手机都还没发明呢
The last time I did this, cell phones didn't exist.
该死
Shit!
爸爸
Daddy.
妈妈快看  是爸爸
Look, Mom, Daddy!
该死
Shit!
见鬼
Oh, fuck!
凯菈
Kara?
来追我啊
Gonna have to find me.
凯菈
Kara?
谢谢  珊兰达  你帮了我大忙
Thank you, Sheranda. You've been very helpful.
我对你服务的评价是3A
You get a Triple A-plus in my book.
你也保重  拜拜
Oh, you take care, too. Okay, yeah, bye-bye.
电话打通了  救援马上就到
So, that was AAA on the phone and they should be here in a jiffy.
还记得这首歌吗
Does this song sound familiar?
你跳得很好
You were such a good dancer.
你被淘汰的时候我很遗憾
I felt so bad when you got voted off.
谢谢
Thank you.
但我还是得说你真人比电视上性感多了
But I have to say you're much sexier in person.
好了  行了  苏珊
Okay. Calm down there, Susan.
伙计  她想跟你大干一场
Dude, she wants to fuck you big time, dude.
-你得招架住哦  -没门
- You got to hit that. - No fucking way.
这是为了吉姆  别那么自私
Do it for Jim, dude, don't be selfish.
你知道吧  我想我要去下洗手间
Hey, you know what? I think I have to go to the bathroom.
凯菈  这不好玩
Kara, this is not funny.
凯菈  快出来
Kara, come on! Kara, come out.
天哪
Oh, my God!
好吧  快来
Okay, hey, come on.
好吧  好吧
Okay, one... Okay, all right...
快来  好的
Come on. Okay, good.
你找不到我
You never could find me.
吉姆  我不想吓你  但是时间不多了
Jim, I don't mean to alarm you but you don't have much time.
是的  我知道
Yes, I know.
-我喜欢你的围巾  -好吧
- I like your scarf. - Okay.
-我喜欢你的大胸  -门
- I like your breasts. - Door.
可以拍个照吗
Would it be okay if I get a picture?
当然
Sure.
我就放在这的
I know it's in here somewhere.
好吧 一瓶发胶
Okay, a bottle of hair spray...
你们还好吧
You guys all right?
没事
Yeah. Yeah.
你知道吗
You know something?
我真佩服你的洗手间里的马桶能那么干净
I really was admiring how clean your toilet was in your bathroom.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道吗  我也要用下洗手间
You know what? I have to use the restroom, too.
你不行
No, you don't.
躺床上去
Let's get in bed.
你不跟我一起吗
Come on and get in bed with me?
不  我不要
No, I'm not getting in bed...
来吧  跟我一起
Come on. Get in bed with me.
不  我不能  凯菈  我的天啊
No, I'm not... Kara, please. Oh, God. Please.
该死
Oh, shit!
硬条  你在这干嘛
Stifler, what are you doing here?
-我只是想来看一眼  -不行
- I just wanted another glimpse. - No.
你怎么给她穿上衣服了伙计
Why'd you put her clothes back on, dude? Boo.
你快走
You have to go.
那是什么
What was that?
像是从外面传来的
That sounded like it came from outside.
从凯菈房间传来的
No, that came from Kara's room.
天哪
Oh, Jesus.
凯菈
Kara?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
快走  快走
Go, go, go!
到底发生了什么
What the hell's going on in here?
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get back in?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
你不记得
You don't remember?
是什么声音
What was that sound?
我不知道
I don't know.
你什么意思  你不知道
What do you mean, you don't know?
我不知道
I don't know.
你喝醉了  是吗
You've been drinking, haven't you?
没有
No.
凯菈  我告诉过你那些男生想把你灌醉
Kara, I told you these boys try to get you drunk
然后占你便宜
so they can take advantage of you.
我知道这些  爸爸
I'm old enough to know that, Dad.
我可不想为了
Yeah, well, I don't want to go to jail
揍那些臭小子而进监狱
for kicking some horny kid's teeth in
但是我会的  相信我
but I will, believe me.
你是什么
What is that?
那是小牛先生
Oh, that's Mr. Moo!
你能把它递给我吗  爸爸
Will you get him for me, Daddy? Please.
我不会生我宝贝气的
I can't be mad at my angel.
生日快乐  我的小公主
Happy birthday, princess.
谢谢爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
没干什么
Nothing.
天啊
Oh, jeez.
硬条
Stifler?
在这儿  伙计
Up here, dude.
我跟你说过我是专家
I told you I was an expert.
该死
Oh, shit.
又发生了什么
What the hell is going on now?
想去看贾斯丁·比伯的演唱会吗
Want to go to a Justin Bieber concert?
吉姆
Uh... Jim?
硬条  快点
Stifler, come on. Come on!
我们走
Let's go.
你们俩待在这
You and you, stay here.
别推我
Don't push me.
我的天啊
Whoa! Oh, my God.
凯菈  你在哪
Kara, where the hell are you?
我在去你家路上
I'm on my way to your place and...
我了个
What the...
该死
Fuck!
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
天哪
Oh, God!
猪头
Hey, stud.
我想你从来没有
I thought you'd never...
该死  我们本来要
Oh, shit, shit. We were supposed to...
没关系
No, it's fine.
什么  不  老天  很不好
What? No, God, it's not fine.
米雪  对不起  我真的  我只是想
Shoot! I'm so sorry, Michelle. I really... I wanted to, I just...
我要把小伊送到我奶奶家
I'm going to drop Ev at my grandma's
我下午就回来
and I'll be back this afternoon.
米雪  等一下
No, Michelle, hold on.
吉姆  我有点担心
Jim, I'm worried.
你担心什么
What are you worried about?
我们走不到一块
Just we're like so out of sync.
我只是
I just...
我不知道我们还能坚持多久
I don't know how much longer we can go on like this.
我保证我会尽全力补偿你
I promise you I will do everything I can to make it up to you.
好吗
Okay?
硬条今晚要办一个派对
Stifler's having a party tonight.
我知道这听起来不怎么浪漫
Okay, I know that doesn't sound romantic or anything,
但是想想我们的第一次
but remember our first time
就是在硬条派对上发生的
was at a Stifler party.
你把我弄得那叫一个惨
You made me your bitch.
是的  是的
Yes. Yes, I did.
要射的时候说一声  好吗
Tell me when, okay?
这他妈怎么回事
What the fuck?
蜜儿这个女孩子
So, Mia.
她挺无拘无束的
She's a free spirit.
不止这样
She's something else.
是的
Yeah, she is.
等一下  你吃醋了吗
Wait a minute, do I sense a little jealousy there?
-没有  -没有吗
- No. - No?
别忘了  是你跟我分手的
Hey, don't forget, you were the one who broke up with me
你去了医学院之后
before you went to med school.
你去了洛杉矶后就一去不返
Hey, you were moving to LA with no return in sight.
你不能怪我想要安定下来
You can't blame me for wanting to settle down.
我没有
No, I don't.
我只是不希望你已经定下来了
I just don't want you to settle.
看看是谁在吃醋
Look who's jealous now.
我不能说和朗定了
I wouldn't call being with Ron "Settling."
他只是虚有其表
Oh, no, he's gorgeous on paper.
这什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
没什么
Nothing.
对不起  你是对的
I'm sorry. You're right.
我的确是在嫉妒
I am a bit jealous.
你知道  这很好笑
You know, it's funny.
从某些方面来说  你完全变了一个人
In some ways, you've completely changed,
某些方面你又完全没变
and, in other ways, you're exactly the same.
海瑟  你可以相信这点
Heather, you can believe this,
什么都没有改变
nothing's changed.
天哪
Oh, my God.
克里斯?奥斯莱克
Chris Ostreicher?
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
能合个影吗
Can I get a pic?
当然
Sure.
爸爸
Dad?
-爸爸  -吉姆
- Oh, hey, Dad. - Hey, Jim.
我要出去一下
I'm just going to run out for a sec.
我在看你的成人礼录像带
I was just watching your old Bar Mitzvah tape.
我拿到你的犹太围巾了
I got your Jew scarf!
还给我  硬条
Give it back, Stifler.
托你的福我是世上最幸福的人
I think I'm the happiest man in the world thanks to you.
我也很想她  爸爸
Yeah, I miss her too, Dad.
我知道
I know.
爸爸  你总是为我提供建议
Dad, you've always been there to give me advice.
但是你如果想说什么
But if there's anything that you want to talk about,
我都愿意听
I'm here for you.
我想我没有什么
Yeah, I don't think there's anything
真的想说的  吉姆
I really need to talk about, Jim.
你觉得现在是时候
Do you think maybe it's time for you to
为你找个伴吗
meet someone else?
爸爸  没事的
Dad, it's okay.
你现在经历的过程都是非常正常的
What you're going through is perfectly natural.
你知道的  外面有那种服务
You know, there are services out there...
-那种服务  -是啊
- Services? - Yeah.
什么服务
Like what?
-去那种按摩房吗  -那是什么
- A happy ending? - What's that?
因为我不会去的
Because I won't go there.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我不需要  我不需要那种服务  吉姆
I don't need that... I don't need that kind of massage, Jim.
这不是我要的
That's not what I was...
因为你知道  这很危险
Because, you know what, it's dangerous.
你自己指不定会染上什么怪病
And you can pick things up.
而你是绝对不会想知道这些怪病是什么的
You don't even wanna know what you can pick up.
-你莫特叔叔就是这样  -别提了
- Talk to your uncle Mort. - I'd rather not.
他住院两周了
He was in the hospital for two weeks.
真恶心
That's disgusting.
我是说
I was talking about
在线约会服务
online dating services.
不  吉姆
No, Jim.
是啊  在我这个年纪  我觉得不行了
Yeah, right, at my age? I don't think so.
都这么多年没你情我爱的了
I've been out of the game for so long.
当年甚至我甚至都没经历过这个过程
There wasn't even a game back then.
爸爸  别担心  我会帮你牵上线的
Dad, don't worry. I'll hook you up.
你有这种相片吗
Do you have those photos?
在这
Here you go.
我们可能需要一些最近的照片
We might need something a little more recent.
你觉得呢
Do you think?
你有更性感的装扮吗
Do you have something that's a bit sexier?
明白了
Gotcha.
你有没有
Did you...
最爱的音乐
Favorite music.
赫尔曼隐士乐队
Herman's Hermits.
好的
Okay.
姑娘们  一个个来
Girls, one at a time, please.
兴趣和爱好
Interests and hobbies.
数独
Sudoku.
我们一会再填
We'll come back to this one.
我们是不是拔得太多了
Are we sure we're not taking off too much?
这些毛毛虫可都是我的标志
These caterpillars are kind of my trademark.
好了  完美
Okay... Perfect.
让我看看  我有点紧张
Take a look. I'm nervous.
太棒了
Oh, that's fantastic!
真好看
That is a great look for me!
简洁的线条  还能移动
Leaner lines. I still have mobility.
我三十年前怎么不这么做
Why didn't I do this 30 years ago?
看起来不错
Looking good.
我们今晚去试试新造型吧
Why don't we test this new look out tonight?
可是硬条今晚要举办个聚会
The thing is, Stifler is throwing a party tonight.
好吧  那下次吧
Oh! Well, another time.
你可以跟我们一起去
But you could come with us.
出去走走会感觉很不错
It would be nice to get out of the house.
但是我得警告你
I do have to warn you, though,
硬条的聚会可能有点
Stifler's parties can get a little
疯
wild.
这是他妈是什么东西
What the fuck is this?
谁把音乐换了
Who the hell changed the music?
对不起  我觉得这个更适合孩子
Sorry, we thought this was more baby-friendly.
对吗  没错
Didn't we? Yes, we did.
大屌硬条
Stifmeister!
呸
Bluck!
颤个胸
Chester!
你们俩小子最近在忙什么
What have you cock-smokers been up to?
-我们刚刚订婚了  -是的
- Well, we just got engaged. - Yeah.
什么  这他妈太基了
What? That's so fucking gay.
硬条  我们就是同性恋
Yeah, Stifler, we are gay.
曲棍球队一半都是基佬
Half the lacrosse team was gay.
你知道的  对吧
You must have known that, right?
伙计  道格和巴里洗澡的时候你进去了
Dude, you walked in on Doug and Barry in the shower.
我以为他们在摔跤
I just thought they were wrestling.
他们确实在摔♂跤
They were.
对啊  确实是
Yeah, they definitely were.
不过那天晚上没有失败者
There just wasn't a loser that night.
这里真的是硬条家吗
Are we sure this is Stifler's?
冷盘
Hors d'oeuvres!
把这个交给主人吧  儿子
Why don't you give this to our host, son?
我的天啊  看看是谁
Oh, my God! Look who it is.
昨晚很抱歉打扰你们
Sorry for interrupting you guys last night.
顺便说下  非常棒
Bravo, by the way.
大多数女人结婚后就不那么做了
Most wives stop doing that after they get the ring.
-你们在说什么  -你染了发吗
- What are you talking about? - Did you change your hair color?
你那个喜欢熟女的朋友今晚来了吗
So, is your buddy, the other MILF guy, here tonight?
我觉得你们总是一起来的
I thought you always come to these things together.
这么说吧  我们已经分道扬镳了
Let's just say that friendship is a two-way street.
很抱歉
Excuse me.
这派对还能再烂点吗
Could this party get any lamer?
没有那么差吧
It's not so bad.
要来点刺激吗
You want some E?
不要  你怎么把这东西弄来了
No. Why do you have that?
这里的其他人都没有
No one else here probably has any.
你确定你不要吗
Are you sure you don't want one?
是啊
Yeah.
不要  要
No... Yes.
不要
No.
好吧  我都吃了
Okay. Fine. More for me, then.
他们在那
And there they are.
小芬
Finchy.
你们在这啊  看看  你们能相信吗
There you guys are. Look around. Can you believe this shit?
老兄  很好嘛
Yeah, man. Nice work.
给你的
For you.
我拿这玩意做什么
What the hell am I supposed to do with this?
那可是正经的红酒  硬条
That's called wine, Stifler.
不不  别在我的舞会上喝
No, no, no, no, not at my party.
我给大家来点烈的
I'm going to get us some shots.
凯文
Hey, Kev.
我能跟你们谈谈吗
Can I talk to you guys for a sec?
好的  在这等我  我马上回来
Yeah, sure. Wait here, I'll be right back.
东西带过来没
So, you brought the goods?
在这呢
Right here.
我想看看
I want to see.
那群蠢货去哪了
What the... Where did those fuckers go?
你好  斯蒂文
Hello, Steven.
-莱文斯汀先生  -是我
- Mr. Levenstein. - Yes.
你也来了
You made it.
真高兴看到你们都回来了
It is so great to see all you kids back in town.
你今天晚上办的宴会棒极了
And what a terrific soiree you're throwing here tonight.
简直太棒了
Just wonderful!
跟你说  我他妈要灌死你
You know what? I'm going to get you fucked up.
干一杯
Have a shot.
不  不  不
Oh! No, no, no.
别这样  斯蒂文  我不怎么会喝酒
I don't think so, Steven. I'm not much of a drinker.
-干了  干了  -不  我不行
- Drink it. Drink it! Drink it! - No, I can't.
干了吧  干了吧
Drink it! Drink it!
棒极了  咱俩再干一杯
Awesome! Let's do another one.
我不能再喝了
I don't think so.
听着  凯文  你还不确定到底发生了什么
Look, Kev, you don't know for sure if anything happened.
我醒来发现她躺在旁边
I woke up next to her in bed,
我们俩还都光着身子
and all our clothes were off.
不管发生什么  我都很内疚
I mean, whatever happened, I feel guilty.
凯文  在法国
Kevin, in France,
只有被老婆当场捉奸
it's only considered cheating
你才算是不忠
if your wife catches you in the act.
她也在这
She's here.
我得走了
I gotta go.
好吧  准备好
All right, get ready.
等一下  等一下
Wait for it. Wait for it!
等一下
Wait for it!
开喝吧
Here she comes!
真他妈强  莱文斯汀先生
Fuck yeah, Mr. Levenstein!
大爷我叫诺亚  小王八蛋
The name is Noah, motherfucker.
这沙发真舒服
Feel the sofa.
这么光滑
It's so smooth.
摸起来就像蓝精灵的屁股
It feels like a Smurf's ass.
来爽一下
Did you feel it?
好吧  蜜儿  你能...
Okay. Mia, can you...
各位  我们来迟了
Hey, guys. Sorry we're late.
我给大家带了点东西
Hey, I got a treat for everybody.
今晚让大家饱饱眼福
I picked something up.
热舞明星第六季
Celebrity Dance Off, Season Six.
看你的了  克里斯?奥斯莱克
My man, Chris Ostreicher.
老天啊
Oh, my God.
我们一定得看看
We have to watch this.
谁想看我的宝贝扭屁股
Who wants to see my baby shake his booty?
反正人家想看
I know I do.
犹太约会网  你在开玩笑吧
JDate? You have to be kidding me.
如果你想操上好逼
If you want quality vag,
你就得多出门野去
you have to go out into the wild.
"逼"
"Vag"?
那是什么  一半阴道么
What is that, a half of a vagina?
我们年轻的时候都叫鲍鱼
You know, in my day we called it a beaver.
我告诉你  我还抓住过一两只
And let me tell you something, I snagged a pelt or two.
那是当然
I bet you did.
老爸
Dad?
吉姆  你老爸比你酷多了
Hey, Jim, your dad is so much cooler than you.
硬条  别再给我爸灌黄汤了
Stifler, please stop getting my dad drunk.
没  他在帮我找逼操呢
No, he's just trying to get me some vag.
得了吧
Okay, come on.
让你爸自己选吧
Let the man make his own decisions.
别了  走吧
Stop. Come on.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
我想要你擦亮陈旧的钢枪
I want you to dust off that old dick of yours,
从这里走出去  泡几个妞回来
go out there, and get some ass.
快出去吧
Oh! Just go out there.
我想我能办到
I think I will.
-老爸  别  -我也是这么想的
- Dad, stop, okay? - It's exactly what I'm gonna...
对不起  但是你今晚喝高了
I'm sorry, but you have had a little too much to drink tonight,
-我不会让你...  -不  不
- and I'm not letting you... - No, no.
别  儿子  我就喝了一杯
No, son, I haven't hardly had one drink.
你知道我爱你
And you know I love you.
我确实爱你  但是你得
I do love you, but you need to
蛋定
chillax.
"蛋定"  老爸  你去哪啊
"Chillax"? Dad, where are you going?
你看到他那个样子了吗
Do you see him?
吉姆  吉姆  让他去吧  让他找点乐子
Jim! Jim! Let him go. Let him have some fun.
现在我们也可以找点乐子
And now we can have some fun.
来吧
Come on.
让一下
Excuse me.
对不起  请让下
I'm sorry, excuse me.
这是洗手间吗
Is this a washroom?
你意识不到自己太自以为事的原因
It doesn't even occur to you that you're self-centered
就是因为你太自以为事了
because you are so self-centered and...
等一下  别挂电话
You know what? Hold on a second.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
您是哪位
Who might you be?
我是硬条他妈
I'm Stifler's mom.
我是吉姆他爹
I'm Jim's dad.
别了  混蛋
Later, fucker.
一旦给她甜头
She won't ever get enough
她就得寸进尺
Once she gets a little touch
如果让我来对付她
If I had it my way
你知道我会让她爽翻天
You know that I'd make her say ooooooh
一旦给她甜头
She won't ever get enough
她就得寸进尺
Once she gets a little touch
如果让我来对付她
If I had it my way
天哪  这是我见过的最荒谬的东西了
Oh, my God, this is the most ridiculous thing I've ever seen.
我的初吻就像这样发生
Well my first kiss went a little like this
老兄  你身材棒极了
Dude, you have an amazing body!
大家为克里斯?奥斯莱克大声欢呼吧
Everybody, raise the roof for Chris Ostreicher!
整整一季以来你都做得很好
You have really been bringing it all season long.
不过现在是检验全国观众
But now it's time, Chris,
是否觉得你真配待在这的时候了
to see if America thinks you done brought it.
-准备好了吗  -放马过来吧
- You ready?   - Let's do it.
让我们揭晓答案
Let's see the results.
什么  吉尔伯特?加德弗莱竟然赢了你
What? Gilbert Gottfried and not you?
真他妈操蛋
Fucking bullshit!
克里斯  真遗憾
Chris, I'm so sorry, man.
我们看着你启动  现在该刹车了
Well, we saw you jam. Now, it's time to scram.
你还有什么想对观众说的吗
Do you have any last thoughts for the audience?
大家  我们就看到这吧
Okay, guys, we can probably end it there.
什么  你开玩笑吧  我还没看完呢
What? No, are you kidding? I haven't seen this.
我想我学到的就是我们得对自己
I think what I've learned is to be true
真诚
to myself,
因为这正是舞蹈的精神  真诚的精神
because that's what dancing is, it's truth.
也许
And maybe,
如果我们每个人多跳一会儿
if we just danced a little bit more,
就不会再有战争了
there would be no more wars.
没有战争
No more war!
外交部倒可以认真考虑考虑这条建议
Well, that is a thoughtful take on foreign policy.
别换台  稍后为您带来胡克?霍根的热舞
Stick around. Hulk Hogan gets jiggy-friggy, right after this.
你不会想错过的  千万不要转台
You don't want to miss this. Stick around.
就我看来  我觉得你被骗了
If you want my opinion, I think you got cheated.
没事吧
Are you okay?
你知道吗  当你...
You know,when the...
当你失去对你很重要的东西
when you lose something that's important to you,
那感觉一点都不好
it doesn't feel very good.
奥兹  那只是个真人秀而已
Oz, it's just a show.
我说的不是真人秀
I'm not talking about the show.
海瑟  你在下面吗
Hey, Heather, you down there?
马上到
Um, coming!
天哪
Oh, my God.
等一下  我马上回来
Wait here, I'll be right back.
我都记不清多少次走进斯蒂文的房间
I can't tell you how many times I walked into Steven's room
刚好看到他和其他女孩做爱的场景
and I caught him in the middle of sex with some girl.
至少他是和活生生的人类女孩在做
At least he was with a real, live human girl.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
有一次我走进厨房
I walked into the kitchen once,
我看到吉姆在插一个派
and I saw Jim humping a pie.
那个派瞬间就成了一堆渣渣
He turned the damn thing into a crumble in about two seconds.
我这个能超过你的
I can top that.
有一次我走进卧室
I once walked into my bedroom
看到斯蒂文把我的梳子插进了他的屁股
and I caught Steven sticking my hairbrush up his ass.
而且插进去的还不是手柄的那边
No, and it wasn't the handle side, either.
别  别  别
No, no, no.
像你这样的窈窕淑女不应该贪杯的
A pretty lady like you shouldn't be drinking quite so much.
我也不能喝了
And neither should I.
来跟大麻怎么样
How about a joint, then?
我们不必等上十三年再见面
We don't have to wait 13 years to see each other again.
那倒是
Yeah, true.
我想哪次可以和你一起去冒冒险
And I guess I could come along on one of your adventures.
我是做助手的料吗
Am I good sidekick material?
助手
Sidekick?
你可不止是当助手的料
I think you are a lot more than sidekick material.
出什么事了吗
Is everything okay?
旧的不去新的不来
It's better than ever.
等等  等等
Okay, wait, wait.
这么重要的场合穿这样可不合适
I don't think we're dressed appropriately for the occasion.
穿上这个
Put that on.
你要去哪
Wait, where are you going?
去换衣服  马上回来
To change. Be back soon.
老兄
Dudes!
有何贵干  兄弟
What's up, bro?
大硬条
Big Stiffy?
吹箫皇后小莱
Blowjob Lipstein.
苍天啊  你他妈是在耍我吧
Oh, you have to be fucking kidding me!
怎么了
Excuse me?
好了
Okay.
你他妈在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
你就光想着让我给你吹
You just expect me to blow you?
当然
Yeah!
我要走了
I'm out of here.
等下  等下  等下
Wait. Wait, wait!
听着  我懂了
Look, I get it.
你对你的身材不自信
You're self-conscious about your body.
不用担心  一会我肯定会关灯的
Don't worry. I was going to shut the lights off anyway.
你还是高中时候那个混账
You are the same douchebag that you were in high school.
你就想我为你服务周全
You just expect me to do everything
而我却什么好处都捞不到
while I get nothing?
想得美
Later.
不  不
No, no!
我们做个交易吧
Let's make a deal.
我让你爽  你也得让我爽
I'll get you off, you get me off.
你什么意见
What do you say?
成交
Fine.
不过你得卖点力了
But I am putting you to work.
我操
Holy shit.
吃饭时间到
Chow time!
你在这
There you are!
我一直在找你
I've been looking all over for you.
听着  我们真的得...
Listen, we really need to...
你要做什么
What are you doing?
抓紧属于我的
Taking what's mine.
没  我就想听听你的声音
No, I just wanted to hear the sound of your voice.
一切还好吧  你听起来挺紧张的
Aw, is everything okay? You seem stressed.
紧张
Stressed?
找到你了
There you are!
不  不  不
No, no, no.
我得挂了  不过一会就回你电话
I have to go right now, but I'll call you back in a little bit.
不用担心
Okay. And don't worry,
我不会趁你不在看绯闻女孩的
I won't watch Gossip Girl without you.
我想你  宝贝
I miss you, babe.
我也想你
I miss you, too.
听着  碧琪  关于昨晚
Listen, Vicky, about last night,
那不是我真正想做的
that wasn't me.
发生的事情  你懂的
With what happened, you know.
我不知道  在你看来可能挺正常的
I don't know. It might be normal in your world.
你以为发生什么了
What do you think happened?
我们的衣服都在地板上
Well, all our clothes were on the floor.
那都是因为你喝醉了掉湖里
Yeah, because they were soaking wet
衣服才全湿透了
from when you got drunk and fell in the lake.
我照顾的你
I took care of you.
所以我们没做爱
So, we didn't have sex?
当然没有
Of course not.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God!
我真高兴原来你这么高看我
I'm glad you think so highly of me.
不是
No.
碧琪  等等
Vicky, wait.
哦  老天啊
Oh, yeah! Oh, my God!
蜜儿  停下来
Mia, stop.
哦  老天啊
Oh, my God, yeah!
蜜儿  快下去
Mia, get off!
我要丢了  要丢了
I'm about to! I'm about to!
海瑟
Heather.
怎么搞的
What the hell?
你和这个骚货有一腿
You have something going on with this skank?
你叫谁骚货呢  你个臭婊子
Who are you calling a skank, you fucking bitch?
住手  住手
Stop it! Stop!
快住手
Stop it!
他妈的
Ow! What the fuck?
那是我才接的发  疯婊子
That's my extension, you bitch!
你个狗日的
You motherfucker!
不要  蜜儿  快住手
No, Mia! Wait a minute!
顺便说一声  我操过马里奥?洛佩兹
By the way, I fucked Mario Lopez!
该轮我了吧
Okay, it's my turn now.
这次可不行
Uh-uh. Not this time.
我们说好的呢
Wait, what about our deal?
让你也尝尝这种滋味  大硬条
Now you know how it feels, Big Stiffy.
好恶心
Gross!
我他妈要吐了
Fuckin' yuck!
你没真以为我又睡着了吧
You didn't actually think I'd fall asleep again, did you?
只要你是我的  我就很开心了
As long as you're mine, I'm happy.
老天啊  凯菈  你在这干什么
Jesus, Kara. What are you doing here?
你那个猥琐的朋友邀请了我和所有姐妹
Your creepy friend invited me and all my girlfriends.
装备不错  原来你还有这个癖好啊
Nice outfit, by the way. Very kinky.
糟了
Oh, shit.
别担心  我反锁了
Don't worry. I locked it.
老天啊
Oh, Jesus.
你们他妈的在这搞什么鬼呢
What the hell kind of freaky shit is going on in here?
AJ  你来这做什么
AJ, what are you doing here?
我跟着你  我得亲眼看到才瞑目
I followed you. I had to see it with my own eyes.
你先搞坏了我的水上摩托
First you fuck with my jet ski,
现在你又来搞我女朋友
then you fuck my girlfriend?
不  老天啊  没有  什么都没发生
No! God, no! Nothing happened.
你死定了  桑德勒
You're going down, Sandier.
桑德勒  搞什么
Sandier? What the...
老天啊
Jesus Christ!
我要把你碎尸万段
I'm going to kill you!
吉姆  你他妈穿着什么鬼东西
Jim, what the fuck are you wearing?
听我解释啊  老天
Hey, I can explain everything! Jesus!
快起来  垃圾
Come on! Shit!
站起来  你这挨操的货
Get up, gimp!
行了  我不会和你打架的  好吗
Come on, I'm not fighting you, okay?
这太蠢了  我是个成年人
This is silly. I'm an adult.
真的吗
Oh, really?
在我看来你就是个任人骑的娘们
Because to me you look like a little bitch pussy.
爷们点  吉姆
Don't be a pussy, Jim.
听着  AJ  冷静下来  好吗
Look, AJ, just calm down, okay?
谁给你们的狗胆
What makes you little fuckers
让你们敢在我大屌硬条家撒野
think you can crash one of the Stifmeister's parties?
你刚才是不是说你是大屌硬条
Did you just refer to yourself as "The Stifmeister"?
这是我所听过最傻的名字了
Because that's the lamest name ever!
我要他妈的宰了你
I'm going to fucking kill you.
放马过来吧
Bring it on.
史蒂夫  得了吧  这太可笑了
Hey, Steve, come on, this is...
你以为你能逃哪去
Where do you think you're going?
别和99级学长过不去  贱人
Don't mess with the Class of '99, bitch!
芬治
Finch!
别伤害我朋友
Don't hurt my friend!
放开我丈夫  你这臭小子
Get off my husband, you little piece of shit!
糟了  条子来了
Oh, crap! It's the fuzz!
我们得逃出去  怎么逃出去
We have to get out. How do you get out?
我需要逃跑路线
I need an escape route!
糟了
Oh, shit!
你想和他在一起
You want to be with him?
好了  成全你们
Fine! He's all yours.
快跑  兄弟们
Come on, man!
吉姆  出什么事了
Jim, what's going on?
都是我的错  我可以向你们解释的
I am so sorry for all of this. I can explain.
昨晚我碰巧遇到我们邻居凯菈
Last night I ran into Kara, our neighbor.
她喝醉了开不了车  所以我把她送回家
She was too drunk to drive, so I drove her home.
然后她开始脱她的衣服  摸我的...
And she started taking off her clothes, and touching my...
我知道不好听
Okay, I know it doesn't sound good,
但是什么都没发生  好吗
but nothing happened, okay?
我根本不在乎她
I don't care about her at all!
真谢谢你了
Thanks a lot.
不  凯菈  等等  我不是那个意思
No, no, Kara, wait. I didn't mean...
别走  米雪  等一下  等一下
Wait, Michelle. Hold on, hold on.
不是你想的那样  好吗
It's not what you think, okay?
我发誓  我就是想把事办好  但是...
I swear, I was just trying to do the right thing, and I...
你得相信我  米雪  求求你了
You have to believe me, Michelle, please.
不管是不是真的
Whether I believe you or not,
我都很失望
I'm disappointed.
我要回娘家住一段时间
I'm going to stay with my grandmother.
别走  米雪
Hold it, Michelle.
别  吉姆
No, Jim.
打架的都跑了  老兄
Hey, the fight's over, guys.
我们不是来管斗殴的
We're not here to stop a fight.
我们是来找被偷的摩托车的
We're here about that stolen motorcycle.
这辆的车辆识别码刚好匹配
Looks like the VIN numbers match up.
保罗?芬治
Paul Finch.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
太牛逼了
Awesome!
搞错了吧  警官
Excuse me, officer.
那是他赌赢了阿根廷的世界杯冠军赢的车
He won that bike betting on the World Cup in Argentina.
你们一定搞错了
You made some sort of mistake.
保罗  到底怎么回事  都怎么了
Paul, what's going on? What is this about?
保罗
Paul.
芬治  给他们讲清楚
Finch, just tell them.
保罗
Paul!
狗屎  今天晚上
Hey, shitbreak, when you're
被狱友蹂躏的时候
getting rammed by your cellmate tonight,
想想凯文
think of Kevin.
米雪  我能...  求你了
Michelle, can I just... Please!
老爸
Dad? Ah!
Dad?
老爸  你在搞什么
Dad, what are you doing?
你没见过我  我没来过这
You didn't see me! I'm not here!
我没来过
I'm not here!
他还好吧
Is he all right?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们要怎么救芬治
What are we going to do about Finch?
去芬治他妈的  让他在监狱过夜吧
Fuck Finch. Let him spend the night in jail.
别这样  硬条
Come on, Stifler!
你这也算朋友
Some friend you are.
别给我提朋友
What about you guys?
你们不给我打电话  不给我发邮件
You don't call me, you don't e-mail,
不在我脸书主页上回复
you don't comment on my Facebook page.
你们甚至都不让我知道
You guys didn't even let
你们是为了高中重聚才回来的
me know you were coming back for the reunion.
那是因为我们知道
Because we knew, somehow,
不管怎样你都会把事情搞砸的
you would find a way to screw things up.
都是我的错  吉姆
Oh, I'm sorry, Jim.
我他妈想让大家这周末过得爽一点
I wanted us to have a fucking fun time
就像我们以前在高中时一样
this weekend, like we did in high school.
但是我们都不是高中生了
But we're not in high school anymore.
你太过执念于过去了  硬条
You are so trapped in the past, Stifler.
你什么时候才能意识到
When are you going to realize
一切都不会变成原来的样子呢
that things will never be the way they used to be?
好吧
Fine.
我猜聚会该结束了
Guess the party's over.
你们这帮混球
Dicks.
昨天的聚会棒极了
Well, that was a great party.
实话实说我真玩爽了
I honestly think I had fun.
好吧  至少还有个人爽了
Well, that makes one of us.
米雪有没有给你打电话
Have you heard from Michelle?
没  她不想和我说话
No. She doesn't want to talk to me.
今晚的重聚怎么办
What about the reunion tonight?
她说她可能来也可能不来
She said she may or may not come.
你们俩怎么了
What's going on with you two?
吉姆  你有什么想和老爸聊的吗
Jim, is there anything you want to talk about?
好吧
Okay.
你和老妈
How often
多久...
did you and Mom...
那个那个
You know?
这就是问题所在
Is that what this is about?
你和米雪已经不...
You and Michelle haven't been...
最近都没
Not lately, no.
你是不是
Is it
不举了
an erectile problem?
有时你可以用你灵巧的大拇指
Because sometimes you can buy a little time
争取点时间
with a well-placed thumb.
-老天啊  -我只是说说看
- Oh, God. - I'm just saying.
-我那里没问题  -不是这个问题
- I don't think that's it. - That's not it?
这可是我们家的独门秘诀
Oh! That's something to keep
可从来没有失手过
in your back pocket, because that's a no-fail.
让我们换个话题吧
Okay, let's be done with that.
本来一切都好好的
No, things in that department were fine.
然后伊凡出生了
And then Evan was born
我们俩就停了
and we kind of stopped.
我们自从那就没做过了  你知道吧
And they haven't really picked up since, you know?
这不成问题  别担心
This is not a problem, so do not worry.
-你能理解  -是的  听着  吉姆
- You understand? - Yeah, listen, Jim.
在你出生之前
Before you were born,
你妈妈和我就像干柴遇到烈火
your mother and I, we would do it every day.
我不想听这个
I don't need this.
有时每天要两三次呢
Sometimes two or three times a day.
那都是七十年代的事了
This is back in the '70s.
我们试验了许多不同的体位
A lot of experimentation was going on.
你老妈最爱一招她叫做"全身总动员"的
Your mother favored something she called, "Diving for dollars."
老天啊  对不起  我不想听
Holy shit. I'm sorry, I don't need...
没关系  我们可以...  我懂了
That's fine, we can... I get it.
我可以给你将给其他的
I don't have to go on with that.
我的重点是当你有了孩子
But my point is, when you have a kid,
你们就为人父母了
you become a dad and a mom.
但是更重要的是不要忘记你们还是夫妻
But it's very important not to stop being a husband and a wife.
如果你们记着这点  爱就能继续做下去
And if you do that, the sex will come.
这倒挺有道理的
That actually makes a lot of sense.
但是你不能等到你们俩都独处的时候
But you can't just wait for the two of you to be alone.
你得自己创造独处的机会
You have to make your own alone time.
你以为你为什么一周去三次希伯莱语学校
Why do you think you went to Hebrew school three times a week?
每周日中午到下午三点
Sundays, noon to three?
每周二下午四点到七点
Tuesdays, four to seven?
我懂了  老爸
Okay, I get it, Dad.
如果你懂了  怎么还会出问题
If you get it, then why the questions?
对不起
I'm sorry.
现在经历瓶颈的人是你  对不起
You're going through this, I am sorry.
我应该好好听着的
I should be listening.
没  是我反应过度了  是我的错
No, I'm overreacting. I'm sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
再次  真的
Again. Really.
欢迎随时咨询
Anytime.
欢迎各位
Welcome, you guys.
听着  找到你们的姓名牌  坐对位置
Listen, find your nametag, find out what table you're sitting at.
阿什丽  见到你真高兴  老天啊
Ashley, so good to see you! Oh, my God.
比利  老天啊  你看起来可真苗条
Billy! Oh, my God, you're looking so svelte.
你以前可有点病态的肥  我还担心你呢
You used to be morbidly obese. I was concerned.
兄弟们
Hey, guys.
-吉姆  -奥兹
- Hey, Jim. - Oz.
蜜儿在哪
Where is Mia?
今早飞回去了
She flew out this morning.
真遗憾  伙计
I'm sorry, man.
米雪怎么样
What about Michelle?
还不太确定呢
I am not sure yet.
芬治
Finch!
怎么回事
What happened?
我给警局打了无数通电话了
I called the police department, like, a thousand times.
谢谢了凯文  我妈已经保释我了
I appreciate that, Kevin. But my mom, actually, bailed me out.
哥们  我搞砸了
Guys, I screwed up.
那车是我老板的
That bike belongs to my boss.
他本来说给我涨工资的  后来反悔了
And I was promised a raise, and I didn't get it,
我就把他的车顺走了
so I simply borrowed it.
其实我活的挺无聊的
The truth is that my life isn't interesting at all.
就是个办公用品店的助理经理
I am an assistant manager at a Staples
在新泽西州巴荣纳市
in Bayonne, New Jersey.
你们是我最好的朋友  抱歉跟你们撒谎了
I lied to my best friends, and I'm sorry.
芬治  你为个无聊工作
You know, Finch, just because you sold out
就把自己卖了  我们大家都差不多
and got a boring job like most of us,
这没什么好尴尬的
that doesn't mean you should be embarrassed.
伙计  这都没什么
Hey, come on, man. None of that shit matters.
这对我意义重大  先生们
That means a lot, gentlemen.
你胳膊到底怎么回事
What about your arm?
开车时把咖啡洒胳膊上了
I spilled coffee on myself while I was driving.
不是吧
No.
倒真是疼死哥了
It hurt like a bitch, though.
那必须的  天哪  芬治
I'll bet. Jesus, Finch.
你们几个  看看这个
Hey, check this out, you guys.
那会玩的可够疯的  看看我们
Crazy, huh? Look at us.
全是回忆
A lot of memories.
史蒂夫?硬条
"Steve Stifler."
希望能和兄弟们一直派对下去
"Hopes to keep the party going with his boys."
有人看到他了吗
Any sign of him yet?
我觉得他不会主动出现的
I don't think he's going to show.
硬条
Stifler?
你们怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
我们问了你妈
We asked your mom.
没  这次我可啥都没干
No. I didn't do anything.
我们是来道歉的  昨晚跟你说的话
We wanted to apologize for what we said last night.
我们不是故意的
We didn't mean it.
怎么不是  我知道了
Yeah, you did. I get it,
你们觉得我就是个二逼
you guys think I'm a dick.
是  好吧
Okay. Well.
你大概是有点二逼
Maybe you are kind of a dick.
但是
But,
你逗的一逼
you're a fun dick.
你正是我们的硬条啊
And you're our dick.
是啊伙计  要不是你
Yeah, man. You were like one of the biggest reasons
高中得无聊死
that high school was awesome.
是啊  高中过的确实棒极了
Yeah, high school was awesome.
然后大家就都毕业了  工作了
Then we graduated and everybody started getting jobs
结婚  生孩子
and getting married and having kids
乱七八糟的破事
and all that other stupid shit.
再看我  我倒显得白痴了
Now, look at me. I'm the bitch of this place.
听着  硬条  家家有本难念的经
Look, Stifler, none of our lives are perfect.
我的最难念
Especially mine.
但我们不如继续派对下去
But what do you say we keep this party going,
一起搞次开心的同学会如何
and hit up this reunion together?
这里到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
天哪  看看这白痴
Oh, my God. This is the jackass.
活堆的山高  你还在这里干什么
You're not even close to being finished and you're up here
和你的小团伙耍酷吗
"Chilling with your posse"?
抱歉  我们能解释
Sorry, we can explain.
不用了  凯文
No, Kevin.
让我来
Allow me.
对啊  凯文  让他来
Yeah, Kevin, allow him.
你最好解释清楚  殃条
This better be good, Stafler.
我叫硬条  傻逼
It's Stifler, fucker.
你算老几啊
Who the hell do you think you are?
得在马子面前装牛逼是吧
Are you acting tough in front of your girlfriend?
咱俩都知道  她就是图你的钱罢了
Because we both know she's only with you for your money.
难不成还图你的老二吗
Definitely not for your dick.
跟你上过厕所的  都印象深刻啊
Because anybody that's peed next to you
三寸金莲都不到啊
knows it's the size of a leprechaun's pinkie.
你胡扯
That's not true.
你胡扯  我可没胡扯
"That's not true." Oh, yeah, it is.
听着  别以为你办公室漂亮
Look, just because you got a fancy office
就能来鄙视我
and I don't even have a desk
谁是二逼谁心里清楚
doesn't change who we really are.
事实是  你就是个傻逼
The truth is, you're still a dork,
哥要玩死你  那是小菜一碟
and I can still kick your ass.
但我让着你
But I'm not going to.
知道为啥吗
You know why?
因为我可是大屌硬条
Because I'm the fucking Stifmeister.
你再敢跟我吹胡子瞪眼睛的
And if you even look at me again,
哥就拉泡屎在你公文包里
I will shit in your briefcase.
伙计们
Dudes?
还有  我一早上什么都没干
By the way, I had no clue what I was doing with any of this shit,
所以你有的干了
so you got a lot of work to do.
酒后之言  就让我们抛却脑后吧
Can we forget about the things I said when I was drunk
那样无礼  并非我本意
I didn't mean to call you that
记不得你说了什么  记不得你的怒火
I can't remember what was said or what you threw at me
请告诉我
Please tell me
请告诉我为何
please tell me why
为何我的车  在你的前院
My car is on the front yard
为何我穿戴整齐的在床上醒来
And I am sleeping with my cloths on
-惊喜  -你来了
- Surprise! - Hey! You made it.
当然了
Of course.
你觉得今年底特律雄狮队怎么样
So what do you think about the Lions this year?
能希望吗
They got a shot?
那得看他们的进攻线如何了
We'll see if their offensive line can hold.
你打算加入热舞明星全明星阵容吗
Are you planning on being on Celebrity Dance Off: All Stars?
我其实还没严肃考虑这事
I actually haven't thought much about that.
你该考虑考虑了
You should think about it.
抱歉  各位  我得走开一下
I'm sorry, guys, you'll have to excuse me.
能打扰一下吗
Can I cut in?
不知道啊  保证不脱衣服不
I don't know. Can you promise to keep your shirt on?
拜托  伙计  就是开个玩笑
Come on, buddy, I'm busting balls.
当然可以
Yeah, of course.
我去拿点喝的
I'll get us some drinks.
好
Okay.
怎么不去跟你女朋友跳舞
Shouldn't you be dancing with your girlfriend?
我和蜜儿  已经分开了
Mia and I are over.
她希望我变成另一个人
She wanted me to be someone else.
变成一个我不喜欢的人
Something that I don't want to be.
那你想要什么  克里斯
What do you want, Chris?
海瑟  我想要现在这样
Heather, I want this.
你和我在一起
I want us.
那你的职业生涯怎么办  洛杉矶
What about your career? LA?
我知道这挺不现实的
Look, I know that it's crazy.
现在我也不知道下一步该做什么
And I don't have all the answers right now,
但我看到你  我就觉得
but I see you, and I just know
我想和你在一起  我爱你
I want you. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you.
当时我正从雪山上滑下来
So, I'm skiing down a mountain.
就看到那男的犯心脏病了
Guy has a heart attack right there.
救了他一命  大事  能谷歌出来的
Saved his life. It was a big story, you can Google it.
是真的
Yeah, it was.
可不是
I bet.
见鬼  不好意思
Holy shit! Excuse me.
等等  这是什么状况
Hey, excuse me. What the hell is going on?
朗  听我解释
Ron, I can explain.
开什么玩笑  就他
Seriously, this guy?
我可是个心外科医生
I'm a fucking heart surgeon,
这家伙连ESPN都没上过
this guy's not even on ESPN.
淡定点  朗
Hey, take it easy, Ron.
你能干什么  打我吗  奥兹
What are you going to do? Hit me, Oz?
要不这样  你干嘛不给我们热舞一段
Oh, I got an idea. What about a dance-off?
这可不是什么真人秀  这是现实生活
This isn't a reality show, okay? This is the real world.
你跟我耍花招  我告你倾家荡产
You take one swing at me, I will sue you for all you're worth.
我可是一钱不值  傻逼
I'm not worth jack shit, Dron.
哥罩你
I'm your dick.
轻松搞定啊
Dropped him!
帅呆了
That was awesome!
听好  我们几天前的晚上突然想到件事
Listen, we had a blast the other night.
你想过做派对策划吗
Have you ever thought about being a party planner?
我们想让你给我们策划婚礼
Because we want you to plan our wedding.
答应吧
Say yes.
好啊  好  非常乐意
Yeah, yeah! I'd love to.
太好了  天哪
Nice! Oh, my God.
谢谢  伙计你太棒了
Thanks! This is great, man.
太感谢了  哥们
Thank you so much. Thank you, bro.
-没啥  -谢谢
- You're welcome. - Thank you.
我得跟你说件事
I have to tell you something.
不用解释
You don't have to explain.
听着  保罗  我喜欢你
Look, Paul, I didn't like you
不是因为你爬了阿尔卑斯山
because you climbed the Alps,
或者徒手杀了匹骆驼什么的
or killed a camel with your bare hands.
我喜欢你  是因为你还和高中一样
I liked you because you were still the same good guy
是真心对我好
that was actually nice to me in high school.
我现在也还是
I'm still that guy.
真的
I really am.
上次我来这里  还是毕业舞会
You know, the last time I was here was for prom.
连舞伴都没有
I didn't have a date.
我也没有
Neither did I.
我得去喝一杯
I gotta get a drink.
什么
What?
我跳的有那么差吗
Was my dancing that bad?
是
Yeah.
凯文  你好啊
Kev! Hey!
你好  杰西
Hey, Jess!
你都有络腮胡了  挺好看的
Look, you have a beard! It looks great.
-是吗 谢谢  -开个玩笑
- Thanks. - I'm kidding.
我们就先说了吧
Let's just get this out of the way.
我是同性恋了  这是我女朋友英格丽
I'm a lesbian now, and this is my girlfriend. This is Ingrid.
-很高兴见到你  -我也是
- Good to meet you. - Nice to meet you, too.
拉拉  我就知道
Lesbians? I knew it!
你俩还不亲一个  证明一下
Why don't you guys make out and prove it.
你一定就是硬条了  早有耳闻啊
You must be Stifler. I've heard a lot about you.
没听到什么好话
Mostly negative.
不错  伙计  搞毛啊
Cool, dude. What the fuck?
杰西卡  见到你很高兴
Jessica, it's good to see you.
高兴才怪
No, it wasn't.
什么狗屁状况
What the...
凯文  你该去和碧琪谈谈
Look, Kev, I think you should go talk to Vicky.
她在那里郁闷好久了
She's really upset over there.
是  谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
男人点  你都有胡子了
Be a real man, you have a beard now.
凯文  别这样  我没事
Kevin, don't. I'm fine.
拜托  我昨天完全是个蠢货
Come on. I was a complete jerk last night.
我伤心是因为你居然那么想我
I was just upset that you would think that I would do that
我都知道你结婚了
knowing that you're married.
我知道你不会
I know you wouldn't.
真的  其实更多的是我紧张了
Honestly, that was more about me being nervous.
又看到你  又想起以前的事什么的
Seeing you again, all these old feelings came up, and...
不知道怎么说  大概就是有点愧疚
I don't know, I guess I just felt guilty.
但我现在还对你有感觉
But the fact that I still have feelings for you
这不正说明我原来是认真的  不是吗
just means that what we had was special.
别误会我
Don't get me wrong, all right.
我很爱艾丽
I love Ellie more than anything.
但不管多少年过去
But no matter how much time passes
你永远是我的初恋
you'll always be my first love.
你也永远是我的初恋
And you'll always be mine.
-凯文  -你好啊
- Kev. - Hey.
尝尝这个小蛋糕  特别棒
You have to try these cupcakes, they're awesome.
艾丽  这是碧琪
Ellie, this is Vicky.
天哪  那个碧琪吗  凯文总跟我讲你
Oh, my God! The Vicky? Kevin has told me so much about you.
他是个好男人  你能有他真幸运
You're a really lucky girl. He's a great guy.
-来和我们跳舞吧  -不  不用了
- Come dance with us. - No, it's okay.
责任不全在我
I can't be held responsible
只因她轻触脸颊
'Cause she was touching her face
责任不全在我
I won't be held responsible
是她先于我  坠入爱河
She fell in love in the first place
无论如何  我无法记得
For the life of me I cannot remember
当年为何  自作聪明  永不屈服
What made us think that we were wise and we'd never compromise
无论如何  我无法相信  我们罪已至死
For the life of me I cannot believe we'd ever die for these sins
我们只是初出茅庐
We were merely freshmen
你好
Hey.
我是吉姆
My name's Jim.
我们一起上的李老师的英语课
We were in Mr. Lee's English class together.
真的吗
Really?
是啊  我  抱歉  真的不记得你
Yeah, I... Sorry, I don't remember you.
好吧
Okay.
我就是大家在网上围观的那个
I was the kid who everyone saw on the internet.
抱歉  还得再具体点
Sorry, you're going to have to be more specific.
我早泄了两次
I pre-ejaculated twice.
-你是吉姆?莱文斯汀  -莱文斯汀
- Oh, Jim Levenstein! - Levenstein
-对的  -对  吉姆?莱文斯汀
- Right! - Yeah, Jim Levenstein.
想起来了
Now I remember. Yeah.
高中之后过得怎样
So, how have you been since high school?
挺好的  挺好的  我想想
Pretty good. Yeah, pretty good. Let's see.
我娶了世上最棒的老婆
I married the most wonderful woman in the world.
生了个世上最可爱的宝宝
And we have the cutest kid ever.
听起来挺完美的
You know what. It sounds like things are perfect.
我愿意尽我所能让它变得完美
I'm willing to do whatever it takes to make it perfect.
当然也包括做世上最性感的老公
And that means being the sexiest husband possible.
真的吗
Really?
米雪  你今天真美
Michelle, you look beautiful.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
想与我共舞一曲吗
Would you like to dance?
荣幸之极
I'd love to.
硬条
Stifler.
卓文  卓结者
Sherman? The Sherminator?
你他妈都干什么去了
What the fuck have you been up to?
结婚  生了一个孩子
Married. Had a kid.
然后离婚了
And divorced.
天哪  真不幸
Oh! I'm sorry.
是挺不幸的
Yeah, I'm sure you are.
也还好  至少我还有小弗朗
But, you know what, at least I got to keep little Furlong.
你用爱德华·弗朗命名你的孩子
You named your kid after Eddie Furlong?
是  知道为什么吗
Yes, I did. You know why?
因为终结者二仍是有史以来最棒的电影
Because Terminator 2 is still the greatest film ever made.
伙计  你严重需要来一炮
Dude, you need to get banged bad.
我要帮帮你
I'm gonna help you out.
你爽过了可以回头再谢我  怎么样
Your cock can thank me later, what do you say?
不用了  我可不打算再上你的当了
No, no. See, I'm not gonna fall for that again.
拜托
Come on.
高中那会  我是挺操蛋的
I know I was bit of a jerk back in the day,
但我已经成熟很多了
but I've grown up a lot since then.
求你了  让我帮帮你
Please, let me help you out.
上当咯
Psyche!
就是跟你开玩笑呢
I'm just messing with you.
来抱一个  你个小流氓
Get over here, you little rascal.
我们来给你找个妞  走
Hey, let's find you some puss-puss. Let's go.
我们不能再待下去了
Okay, we have to get out of here.
-总算  -对
- It's about time. - Yeah.
没什么希望的
It's a lost cause.
女的要么结婚了  要么有对象了
All these women are either married or came with dates.
你好  萝妮
Hey, Loni.
伙计  想不想颠覆下世界观
Dude, how would you like to have your world blown?
后会有期  硬条
Hasta la vista, Stifler.
好了  就剩我一个没女人上
Great, everybody's getting laid but me.
真倒霉
This sucks.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我想找保罗?芬治  你看到过他吗
I'm looking for Paul Finch. Have you seen him anywhere?
你找芬治干什么
What do you want with Finch?
接他回家  他是我儿子
I'm here to pick him up. I'm his mom.
芬治还有个妈
Finch has a mom?
不对  我是说  你是芬治的妈妈
I mean, you're Finch's mom?
是  你是他朋友吗
Yeah. Are you a friend of his?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
保罗可是我铁哥们
Paul is like my best friend.
我爱死他了  现在更爱了
I love him so much. More now than ever before.
我们怎么从没见过  我是史蒂夫?硬条
In fact, I can't believe we haven't met. I'm Steven Stifler.
我是瑞秋
I'm Rachel.
什么  怎么了
What? What is it?
就是感觉有点诡异
I just got this feeling
好像要坏事
like something really bad is about to happen.
别担心  我会像教堂里的老鼠一样安静的
Don't worry. I'll be as quiet as a church mouse.
吉姆
Jim!
我太想要你了
I want you so bad.
你不知道我也有多想
Oh, you have no idea!
天哪
Oh, God! Oh, God!
天哪  就这样  我快不行了
Oh, God, there it is. I don't think I can hold it anymore.
再坚持会
Hold it in!
抱歉  会的
I'm sorry, I will.
我都忘了这有多爽了
I just forgot how awesome this is.
天哪  就是这样
Oh, yeah, I need this.
老天爷  米雪  我爱死你了
Oh, God, Michelle! Fuck, I love you!
吉姆
Jim?
娜迪亚
Nadia?
抱歉  你俩忙着呢  是吧
I'm sorry. You are busy, yes?
-没有  -是
- No. - Yes.
是  是
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
娜迪亚  见到你很高兴
Nadia, it's so nice to see you,
但那个  能给我们一分钟吗
but do you think you could give us a minute?
三
Three.
三分钟
Three minutes.
好  看你俩相亲相爱的真好
Okay! So nice you are still together.
我看你现在更驾轻就熟了嘛
And I see you've gotten much better at this.
好吧  谢谢
Well, thanks.
那就是吉姆吗  长得一点不像我
That's Jim? He looks nothing like me.
高中的时候  我约过一个曲棍球队长
You know, when I was in high school, I dated a lacrosse player.
其实 不止一个
In fact, I dated a few of them.
真没想到
You don't say.
我总是希望  保罗能更喜欢体育
I always wanted Paul to be more into sports.
但他就是不怎么感兴趣
But he just was never that interested.
不用粉饰什么
You don't have to sugarcoat it.
芬治就是笨手笨脚的很
Finch was a klutz.
是  我也觉得  但那可不是遗传我
Yeah, I guess he was, but he did not get that from me.
我原来可是拉拉队长
I was head cheerleader.
要说我从曲棍球员身上学到了什么的话
And if there's anything I learned from lacrosse players,
就是我喜欢玩棍棍
it's that I like to handle a stick
和爱抚球球了
and cradle those balls.
我爱上你了
I love you.
准备好了吗  硬条
Are you ready for me, Stifler?
必须的
Oh, yeah!
咱们走
Let's go.
米雪
Oh, Michelle.
天哪  米雪
Oh, God, Michelle.
你太棒了
You are amazing!
比浴缸好吗
Better than the bathtub?
好多了
Much.
比这个好
Better than this?
肯定的
Of course.
脱了这些
Oh, take those off!
我们不该这样
We shouldn't be doing this.
就该这样
Yes, we should.
硬条
Oh, Stifler.
芬治他妈
Oh, Finch's mom!
叫我大屌硬条
Call me the Stifmeister!
你就是大屌硬条
Yeah, you are the Stifmeister.
熟女
Milf?
芬治他妈
Oh, Finch's mom!
熟女
Milf.
说我最棒
Tell me I'm the best.
你就是最棒的
You are the best!
熟女
Milf.
-熟女  -熟女
- Milf. - Milf.
芬治他妈
Oh, Finch's mom!
熟女  熟女  熟女
Milf! Milf! Milf!
太爽了  就是这样
Yes! Yes!
你儿子太蠢了
Oh, your son's such a dork!
闭嘴  不许说他
Stop talking about him!
我们头一次同学会  就这么过去了
Well, our first reunion is officially in the books.
我不知道你们怎样  我昨晚上结果可不错
I don't know about you guys, but my night ended pretty well.
棒极了
It was great.
-昨晚上可是爽死了  -难忘啊
- I had a blast. - Unforgettable.
真的是  我射得跟水龙头一样
Fuck yeah! I jizzed like a racehorse.
你晚上干什么去了  硬条
What happened to you at the end of the night, Stifler?
最后和谁过的
Who did you end up with?
绅士从不透露私生活  吉姆
A gentleman never kisses and tells, Jim.
伙计们
Guys?
我一会就过去  好吧
I'll be right back, okay?
凯菈
Kara!
听着  那天的事  真的很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry about what I said the other night.
没事  是我该说抱歉
No, I'm the one who should be apologizing.
没想到我还会干出那种事  尴尬死了
I can't believe the way I acted. I'm so embarrassed.
别
Don't be.
我像你这么大的时候  对性也挺着迷的
When I was your age I was pretty obsessed with sex, too.
我知道
I know.
看到油拖把上那段视频了
I've seen the YouTube clip.
是  大家都看到了
Oh, of course you did.
但是  谢谢你能理解我
But, thanks for understanding.
我回去想了想  你说的对
I was thinking about it, and you're right.
我是该等那个特别的人
I should really wait for someone special.
只是  再找个像你这么好的男人  挺难的
Just, it's going to be tough to find a guy as good as you.
你肯定能找到的
Well, I'm sure you will.
这周末让我焕然一新啊
Well, I feel like a whole new man after this weekend.
不过要分别还是挺不爽的
Kind of sucks we have to leave, though.
我可不走了  我要休假
Not me. I'm going to take some time off my job
多和海瑟待会
and stick around here with Heather for a while.
不错嘛
Nice!
你呢  芬治
What about you, Finch?
我和塞琳娜正打算去欧洲玩
Selena and I, we're planning a little jaunt to Europe.
多和你妈联系联系  她挺想你的
Just make sure you call your mom. She misses you.
你怎么会知道
How would you know?
这就结束了  是吧  要回到现实了
I guess this is it, huh? Back to reality?
我们不该苦等下次同学会才见
We shouldn't wait until the next reunion.
我们该每年都聚一次
We should try to get together every year.
你们怎么想  下次再见
What do you say, until next time?
-下次再见  -下次再见
- Until next time. - Until next time!
他的床第燃烧着爱欲之火
His bed is on fire with passionate love
邻居们抱怨着楼上的响动
The neighbours complain about the noises above
要在上面她才带感
But she only comes when she's on top
我上了芬治他妈
I fucked Finch's mom.
什么
What?
你刚说什么
What was that?
心理医师让我不要再见你
My therapist said not to see you no more
她说你像是不治之症
She said you're like a disease without any cure
她说我痴迷于你  心已掏空
She said I'm so obsessed that I'm becoming a bore
天啊
Oh no
这是怎么回事
What's this?
天哪  亲爱的  别这样
Oh, no, dear. No, no, no.
宝贝  别
No, dear. No!
天哪
Oh, boy. Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
天哪
Oh, my God!
电影不错
Great movie.